So it will be
with the resurrection
of the dead.
The body that is sown
is perishable,
rises imperishable.
It is sown weak.
It is risen with power.
It is sown in dishonor.
It is risen with glory.
It is sown as a natural body,
it is risen as a spiritual.
If there is a natural body,
there is a spiritual body.
That'Ős why I love you, major.
Five klicks north,
we should find a second
division hospital.
Heads up, they hydrated.
We ain'Őt in London no more.
We got trees here,
so watch your six.
Copy that. Yes, Sir.
No more teatime, huh, Major?
No more teatime, Private.
Just remember
this is a quick sweep.
Five, six days,
you could be home having
grits with grandma, Reynolds.
Oh,
my granny makes the best grits
in all of Texas.
Well, you go ahead and tell Nana
she got a new grandson
named Gustavo,
and I want some of them grits.
I wouldn'Őt care much
for your grandma'Ős grits,
but I'Őd love
to meet your sister.
Hey, sonny boy,
you too young for that,
but maybe when
you'Őre older, young gun.
Take cover! Watch your six!
Ammo!
You'Őre a cold-blooded
killer, Sir.
Let me look. You'Őve been
long-bladed, soldier.
Keep some pressure
on that, okay?
All right, okay.Pressure.
All right. Let'Ős see
what we'Őve got.
Hey,
you make sure you call my mom.
She'Ős gonna be mad.
She'Ős gonna be real mad.
Pressure! Listen to me.
We gotta move, gotta go quietly.
Can you make it? Yes, sir.
Up we go. On your feet.
Vic. Hey, you get any rest?
Nah.
You look like shit.Thanks.
Could try and get you
some diphenhydramine
if you'Őd like.
I used to use it to
get to sleep when
my mother-in-law visited.
Let'Ős hope it doesn'Őt
come to that.
Something else?
Saw something else in a crate.
Not sure it was supposed
to be in the supply boat.
Yeah, what? Bourbon.
No, no, no. I need
to keep my head clear.
Probably better. There'Ős
no diphen out here anyway.
I hear we'Őre both up
for double shifts today.
No, no. I heard we got
new personnel
coming in from Hawaii.
That'Ős what I heard too.
Looks like that'Ős not
happening anymore.
This is bullshit. Talk to your friend.
Maybe I will.
Password.
Come on, Jake, it'Ős me.
Good luck, Vic.
General'Ős in a bad mood.
Isn'Őt he always? It'Ős worse.
Worse? Just a warning.
Thanks for the tip.
Password?
I haven'Őt slept for days.
How am I supposed to remember
what the password is?
That'Ős close enough.
Oh wow.
Now this makes me homesick.
Keeps a little
normalcy in my life
in the middle
of all this insanity.
Smoke?
Thanks. I quit.
It helps me with my headaches.
I think that'Ős what
they call addiction.
What do they call this?
Bonus?
I'Őll drink to that.
What can I help you with, Vic?
I just heard that
we'Őre not getting
new surgeons shipped in. I heard the same.
That'Ős a mistake.
We'Őre being overrun
in here.
What do you want me
to do about it?
Plead our case. They'Őre not gonna
listen to me.
They put me out here
so they don'Őt have to
listen to me anymore.
We'Őre a week late
on the morphine.
Troops are our priority.
Yeah, I, I'Őm not
getting any sleep.
I'Őm not the only one.
Everyone'Ős pulling
six shifts without a break.
It'Ős been over a month, Jake.
How'Ős your hand? Still shaking?
Not at the moment.
Well, you keep up this schedule,
don'Őt get enough sleep,
it'Ős gonna get worse
and you'Őre not gonna be
any good to us
as a surgeon,
let alone a soldier,
if you have to pick up a weapon.
Luckily, as a surgeon,
we don'Őt have to
arm ourselves during battle.
Vic,
I'Őll do what I can.
Thanks, Jake.Yeah.
You really should start
easing up on that.
I'Őm getting ready so
I can toast to Jesus
when my time comes.
Isn'Őt that supposed
to be with wine?
Who'Ős keeping track?
Vic,
you'Őll be home soon.
I wish I could say the same.
Secure the patient!
Prepare for surgery.
Roll him in.
Secure the patient,
secure the patient.
Hold his legs down.
Stay still, Kid.
Oh my god! Oh my god! My arm!
I'Őm gonna lose my arm!
Just breathe!
Stay with me, stay with me.
I'Őm gonna lose my arm,
I'Őm gonna lose my arm!
You'Őre gonna be fine,
you'Őre gonna be fine!
The bastard jumped at me! What have you
got here?
Shrapnel to his forearm,
ripped it up pretty bad.
Given him more
than enough morphine
but he ain'Őt taking to it.
The arm? It'Ős hanging on
by a thread.
Needs to be amputated.
What'Ős your name,
Buster? Adell.
Adell, is that your
first or last name?
First. Last name'Ős Dollins.
Dollins? Where you from?
Paris, Texas.
I got a cousin from
Greensville. You ever been?
Yeah.
Hold him down. Secure the legs.
They'Őve got a great
burger joint. Am I right?
Yeah, they do. Yeah they do, they do,
they do, and those Texas girls?
I mean, the Southern
belle is all.
Mine'Ős from Tennessee,
but you know,
you gotta get
one of those, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Southern girls down there.
Huh? Beautiful.
You did good kid, you did good.
You'Őre okay. It'Ős okay.
No, no, no. You'Őre okay.
You'Őre fine. Don'Őt look.
My arm! My arm!
My arm! Get in, get in.
Get back in.
I play ball. What am I
gonna do with one arm?
Right, get him in a room
and get someone
to write a letter back
home for him, all right?
Guys, that'Ős you too.
Let'Ős go.
All right.
Let'Ős cut a rug, sugar.
There we go, people.
There we go. Keep it moving.
God!
Private.
Up you get. Up you get, soldier.
Come on, come on, come on!
Camila, he needs to get
to surgery, now.
We got a gaping
puncture wound here.
Probably a bayonet,
massive bleeding.
Well, you and your friend
are lucky to be alive.
You think? Major Porter,
Staten Island.
Gustavo Esposito, Los Angeles.
Vic Weber, Brooklyn.
Go, go, go, go!
Good work. Thank you.
Gave him some of my
grandfather'Ős vodka.
You smuggling in booze,
young lady?
You haven'Őt had this vodka yet,
have you?
No.
Oh, sorry.
You didn'Őt wake me.
I can'Őt sleep on this
god forsaken island.
Hey, do me a favor.
Go take care of somebody
worse off than me. I'Őm fine.
You sure? Yeah.
Insomnia'Ős a pretty common
problem around here.
Where'Őd you ship in from?
Great Britain.
Can'Őt you tell by my accent?
I could tell you'Őre
from the boroughs.
That'Ős 'Őcause you'Őre
from Brooklyn.Yeah.
But judging by your
lack of accent,
you ain'Őt been there
in a while.
I went out to California,
graduated from UCLA.
That was my next question.
But hey, I did pick up
a little jolly old English
while I was
stationed over there,
comes out when I'Őm mad.
Yeah? I can'Őt hear it.
You will.
How'Ős Gustavo?
Another ten minutes,
he might not have
made it.
Leanne'Ős got a good
bedside manner.
He stands a pretty good chance.
That'Ős good.
Oh! Jesus! What do you give
for pain here, Doc, soda pop?
Easy, easy.
You lost a lot of blood.
They'Őre a quarter inch
away from your kidneys.
Yeah.
Nice wound to match the one
on the other side, right?
I saw that. And a whole bunch
of others.
They tell a story, yeah?
Yeah. All from combat?
Hell no, Doc.
Street fights down at the
Plaza bar by Carrington Avenue.
You ain'Őt been there?
Man. Never heard of it.
You don'Őt get out
to the forgotten boroughs
too much, now, do you?
They have a minor league team
that isn'Őt very good.
I forgot what they were called.
Staten Island Yankees.
A disgrace to their namesake.
Hey, wait. Hey, I tell you what,
when we'Őre outta here,
you meet me in my block
in my neighborhood,
and you put your money
where your mouth is.
You'Őre on.Okay. We got a deal.
Yeah. Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing? Come on.
It'Ős okay.
Who'Ős the officer in charge?
I gotta talk to him.
That would be General Carroll.
That old puffer?
Yep. Makes sense. No wonder
these stitches hurt.
Hey, he does what he can.
Hope you didn'Őt use
that hand on me.
I got it
under control. How'Ős that?
I use a heavy bag.
Heavy bag. Is that right? Wow.
You are from Brooklyn.
Yeah.
Well tell you what, Doc,
you need to take me
to see the general.
It'Ős important.
Sir, I'Őd like to introduce...
You didn'Őt say the password.
Password?
There you go. How'Ős this?
Work for you?
I see you brought the
good stuff over here, sir.
It'Ős my private stash.
Man of good taste.
You live up to the legend.
I needed that.
Awful rude of me
not to introduce myself
before drinking you dry, Sir.
Major Porter.
Just call me Jake.
I know who you are. Well-known
in certain circles, sir.
Well, I was a bit prolific
in my younger years.
Some say that made me a target.
I say that'Ős the whole
goddamn point.
Cheers to that.
What can I do for you, Major?
Well,
I wanted to meet the legend
and to warn you, sir.
Warn me?
Me and my men were doing
a sweep down the hill
and we were ambushed.
Most of us were wiped out
besides myself and the Private
who almost bled to death.
I laid low for a couple hours,
but I overheard one of them
talking about an
attack on this facility
led by Field Marshal Fukuda.
A real nasty son of a bitch,
in case you never
heard of him.
I know who he is.
When'Ős this attack
supposed to happen?
That, I don'Őt know, sir.
I was ambushed again
before I could hear
anything else.
That'Ős where those
fresh wounds came from.
All right.
And what do you want me to do
with this information?
Radio it in, sir?
Well, I can certainly try,
but they don'Őt much care
what happens out here.
Well then, I'Őd say
ready your men.
Take a look around, Major.
We got a few dozen wounded
GIs and half of them
can barely walk,
let alone fight.
You got 127,000 US soldiers
deployed out here
and you'Őre telling
me you can'Őt get
one of them out?
Anything else, Major?
We'Őre sharing a toast
here, sir.
But we have a
situation and this is what
you'Őre gonna do
with the information
you'Őre blessed with?
You'Őre welcome to leave
anytime you want.
Then we'Őre fucked.
And now would be a good time.
But then you have no one, sir.
I'Őm sorry, sir.
No need to apologize, Vic.
That'Őll be all.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Porter. What?
That intel. When'Ős it
supposed to happen?
I don'Őt know.
I can go back and
try to plead your case
to the General.
This ain'Őt no case, buddy.
Look. He'Ős having a bad day
and might be a little drunk.
Don'Őt apologize for him, okay?
It'Ős not your responsibility.
So what do we do?
You ever seen combat?
Don'Őt "Oh" me. I'Őm asking
you a question.
Have you ever been in combat?
Or do you hide behind
your scalpel and your syringe
full of morphine all day?
Yeah, I did my basic training.
That'Ős not what I asked.
Have you ever seen combat?
No.
Patching up kids from Missouri,
it'Ős a lot different
to witnessing
a 50-caliber shell
rip through a man'Ős chest,
and some of these guys
are your friends.
The sound.
That sickening crunch
of blood and bone.
The seconds
that feel like hours.
And then you'Őre waiting.
You'Őre just,
you'Őre waiting
for the next bullet
to hit you
in the back of your
own fucking head
and it'Ős over,
and over, and over again.
I put these kids back together
day in and day out.
I seen what happens
over and over.
Okay. But you ain'Őt seen
what'Ős coming,
and maybe you can
understand why I'Őm so
upset with the General.
This guy used to be
a fucking war hero.
Now,
he'Ős just a shadow of his own reputation
when we need him.
So what do we do?
We evacuate, Doc.
To where? What?
We'Őre understaffed
and we'Őre knee-deep
in wounded guys.
Some of 'Őem can'Őt even walk.
Everybody does their part.
Whoever can fight, fights.
This, this, or this? Yeah.
Are you sure? Sure.
Faster, faster. Do it like
your lives depend on it.
It'Ős not fast enough,
Sergeant, move.
Hey, five bucks if you
kick his ass.
Can you do it?
Can you punch him?
Well, who woke up
the devil, now?
You should be resting.
I, I, I can'Őt.
This is the side I sleep on.
It don'Őt feel so good.
I guess that'Ős it.
I guess I really did
die in here.
Excuse me? Oh, ignore him.
He'Ős been rambling
on like that ever since
he woke up.
I can'Őt believe
what I'Őm seeing here
right in front of me.
Must have died and got
my ass sent to heaven.
Oh no. I promise
you'Őre still alive.
Then how come when I look
around, all I see is angels.
That'Ős because you'Őre in hell.
My apologies if I
offended any of you.
It'Ős okay. It'Ős just
too much morphine.
Not enough.
What happens if I take too much?
Then it'Ős
sweet dreams. Check on you again.
At least I won'Őt have
to pick up a gun again.
Hey, you doing okay?
I think so.
Where'Őd you say you was from?
Paris, Texas?
Yeah. That'Ős right.
Born and raised.
Soldier named Pete,
he'Ős tall, dark hair.
He said his mama was Cherokee.
We were at
Pearl Harbor together.
He took a bullet for me.
He'Ős from Powderly.
That'Ős right outside
Paris, isn'Őt it?
Yeah, I'Őve heard of Powderly.
Yeah. Population,
about a hundred.
Yeah.
That'Ős what he said.
Anyway, you.
You run into him back home,
you tell him Ava says,
"Thank you."
Okay. I will.
I will.
You know you don'Őt have
to hide that from me.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
The Major'Ős a real asshole,
isn'Őt he?
It'Ős how they manufacture 'Őem.
Maybe we should
order a factory recall.
Fortunately, these bastards
tend to get results.
Maybe.
How'Ős that kid doing?
You'Őll need to narrow it down
if you want an answer
I didn'Őt pull outta my ass.
The Southern boy, the amputee.
Oh, him. Big Tex.
Well,
aside from trying to come to terms
with losing an arm,
I'Őd say he'Ős doing
as well as he can
given the situation.
Morphine'Ős really
working wonders
with his inhibitions.
Kid'Ős coming out of his shell.
Who'Ős he flirting with?
Take your pick.
Well, he'Ős out of his league.
He doesn'Őt stand a chance.
He'Ős pretty charming.
You should go watch him
before he passes out again.
Yeah, from the morphine?
From one of them slugging him.
Major, my weapon!
Give me my weapon!
It'Ős okay. It'Ős okay.
Take a breath. Relax.
There you go.
It hurts like hell.
I'Őm sure it does,
but you can handle it.
Where are we? We'Őre in
a hospital facility.
Just outside our perimeter.
We'Őre all good.
They'Őre coming for us?
What the hell was that?
No rest for the wicked.
I'Őm gonna get you home,
soldier.
I'Őm gonna get you home.
I figured I'Őd find
you two out here
without weapons.
We don'Őt get issued guns.
Don'Őt gimme that shit.
You'Őre soldiers!
Arm yourselves!
Oh my God.
They'Őre coming for us.
Shh! Be quiet.
You can fucking
hear that, can'Őt you?
Get your shit together.
McGovern, we got evacs!
Take cover! Take cover!
Get down!
Remember your training.
That was just the first wave.
There'Őll be more whether
we'Őre ready or not.
Doc, what have you got?
I ain'Őt feeling so good.
I got it.
Sir?
Move these people
to a safe space.
Secure.
I need to get back
to my office and burn
all sensitive documents.
Sir?
Yeah. Carry on, gentlemen.
Yes, sir.
It'Ős good to have him back.
So, what next?
We radio for help
and get the hell outta here.
That'Ős a negative.
Not possible.
Why not? It'Ős the first place
they went.
It'Ős in a million pieces.
Is it fixable? I doubt it.
Shit.Okay.
You got a basement level?
Kind of.
Is it big enough
to hold everyone?
Course not. Well, we work
with what we got.
We move in groups.
We need to make a sweep
of this place.
See what we can find.
Who knows this place best?
Most likely we do.Yep.
Okay. You take backup,
take a sweep.
Anything you can find.
Guns, hammers, nails, razor blades,
anything. You got it?
Got it. Got it.
Isaac. Clear the basement.
And give my man here a gun.
Thank you, Major.
You owe me a bottle
a whiskey, Private.
Two bottles
for respect. Sounds good.
You got any flares?
I'Őm sure we do.Okay.
Let'Ős move.
These? Go on, yes, yes.
Come on, hurry. Come on!
Okay.
Mia, on this side, check.
Inessa, over here.
Anything we can use.
Medications,
bandages, weapons. Anything.
Oh, perfect.
Inessa, on this side.
Anything sharp, medication.
Yeah, yes.
Come on, girls, we gotta move.
This is good, right?
Whatever you can carry.
Well, there it is.
There'Ős what? Stress reliever,
right?
By the way, wonderful job
being off the mainland.
That'Ős a potato sack
I found in the jungle.
Filled it with sand,
right? Yeah.
Yeah, well, I'Őll tell you what.
Maybe you can help me fix that
and hang it back up
before we leave,
maybe I'Őll take a few swings.
Well, I think you'Őre gonna
have plenty opportunity
to hit other things
other than a potato sack.
This works. Let'Ős get
'Őem down here.
Get down, get down! Get down!
Move, move, move! Move!
Let'Ős go!
He'Ős hit!
Japanese. Cover me.
Stay with me. Stay with me.
Here you go.
Cover me. Go, go, go, go!
He'Ős gone.
Morphine! I need some
morphine here!
I'Őm coming! You'Őre wasting your time.
Shut up. Stay with me.
Come on, man.
Stay with me.
Stay with me. Shit!
I told you, you were
wasting your time.
That man had a wife
and a daughter.
Everyone has a wife
You hear me? Let it go, Vic.
Listen to your friend.
There'Ős gonna be another
wave coming down here.
And we don'Őt want to be
here when that happens.
He'Ős right. We need to move.
Okay.
Let'Ős see if we can
salvage that thing.
It may come in
handy later, ok. Right away, sir.
Make it happen.
I'Őm gonna clear the holes.
Goddamn it.
Here! Come on, hurry up!
Here, here, move! Here!
Come on, come on!
Let'Ős move, move! Hurry! Hurry!
These are too far apart.
We gotta move
them closer together.
We gotta fit everybody.
Come on, we gotta have
room for everybody, down.
In a row, like this.
First kill?
Just remember something.
If it wasn'Őt him, it was me.
Then it was you. You got that?
Got it.
Too much caffeine?
I know what it is.
It started after I deployed,
I, I can control it.
Thanks for having my back.
I hope to return
the favor. Let'Ős move.
I think, I think I need
a shot of morphine.
Oh.
You have more,
and there won'Őt be any
for the rest of us.
My nerves.
Hey, son, what I tell you?
The nerves ain'Őt gonna
do no good for you
around here.
A shot of morphine
will keep me calm.
is gonna knock you out.
I need you aware,
'Őcause like Major said,
I need you to have
my front and my back.
At least I'Őd die peacefully.
You not gonna die.
You not going die.
Look at me, son.
What'Ős your name?
Adell Dollins.
Adell Dollins. I like the name.
Repeat after me Adell.
I'Őm not going die.
I'Őm not going to die. Ooh, louder, Adell.
I'Őm not going die. I'Őm not going die.
I'Őm not gonna die! I'Őm not gonna die!
Yeah, God got a plan
and look what we got here.
Shit.
Not bad.
Where you from, kid? California.
You should have enlisted.
Could always use a pair
of hands like yours.
I tried. What do you mean,
you tried?
And?
Jesus Christ, that was close.
Y'Őall boys ready?
Hold.
No!
Porter!
I think it went clean through.
You okay?
I know you'Őre not, let'Ős go.
Is he good? Yeah.
Over the shoulder, big man.
There you go. Let'Ős move.
What are you going to do?
You'Őre going to die.
Come on, put me down.
Empty.
Your shoulder, it'Ős not lethal.
I'Őm out.
The General'Ős got guns
in his office.
Give me a hand, come on. Up!
Guys.
He went down fighting.
He died a hero.
It'Ős empty.
Same.
I'Őm gonna lie down guys.
I don'Őt feel so good.
They took everything.
You okay?
No. No.
So it will be with the
resurrection of the dead.
The body that is sown
is perishable is raised
imperishable.
It is sown weak.
It is raised with power.
It is sown and dishonored
is raised in glory.
It is sown as a natural body.
It rises as a spiritual body.
If there is a spiritual body,
there is a natural body.
Corinthians.
That verse got me
through a lot of long nights
since I left home.
How long you been here?
You know.
I used to count the days.
Now, I don'Őt remember
the day I shipped out.
The good thing is
I don'Őt obsess over
time anymore. I just,
I just wanna get home someday.
Yeah. You and me both.
Boroughs coming together, yeah?
Boroughs coming together.
We ain'Őt that different
after all, are we?
No. No, we'Őre not.
How about them out there?
I figure they'Őre just
as scared as we are.
Soldiers following orders.
And I quit.
Why deprive yourself, Doc?
It could be your last
night on this earth.
A forgotten borough
finally making some sense.
Hey. Cuz I'Őm from Jersey?
You know how you could tell
somebody'Ős from Jersey?
How?
They never shut
the fuck up about it.
You don'Őt hear me
denying that one.
Sweet Lord. That tastes
good right now.
There you go, see?
Who says people from Jersey
don'Őt have any taste.
Just don'Őt let my wife know.
She'Őd actually kill me.
She'Őd say I'Őm setting
a piss-poor example
for my kid.
You got kids, Porter?
Me? No.
Not that I know of, anyways.
Oh, is that right?
No, I'Őm just saying that
I did a lot of traveling.
So you know, I wouldn'Őt be
surprised if there'Ős some
hard-nosed little bastard
running around,
out there somewhere
that looks like me.
How about you?
Me and my wife, Jenny,
we want kids.
It'Ős just not in the cards yet.
You didn'Őt try before you left?
Oh, like drunk jackrabbits.
It just didn'Őt happen.
It will. And when it does,
do your best to keep outta
situations like this
'Őcause this ain'Őt
no place for no kid.
That'Ős all we can hope for,
that our kids do
better than we do.
That'Ős what I'Őm
hoping for my boy.
Damn smart kid.
Lot smarter than I was
at his age. Early bloomer.
Now, you just gotta
get him outta Jersey.
At least to UCLA like
this smarmy bastard,
right here.
Oh there it is. There it is.
What'Ős the first
thing you'Őre gonna do
the day you get back?
Who you'Őre talking to,
me or him?
Whoever fucking answers first.
I don'Őt know, he'Ős your buddy.
You tell me.
Hey, be my guest.
Why, you embarrassed?
You hiding something
over there?
I'Őll get it outta you.
Try it. I'Őm Irish.
Me? You know, I never really
thought about it that much.
I'Őm thinking maybe a ball game.
First pitch of the season.
Smell of that fresh green grass,
the tall beer in my hand,
a beautiful woman on my arm.
One of those New
York stadium hot dogs
in my mouth.
Yeah, it'Ős simple.
That'Ős what I look forward to.
Sounds like
the perfect day to me.
How about you?
I'Őm from Jersey.
You wouldn'Őt like it.
Try me.
Would love to take
my wife and kid out.
Stop in each state.
Show them the country.
Travel. Show my boy what
his dad was out protecting.
Show him why.
That sounds nice.
Just skip the rest
of Jersey and parts
of Connecticut.
Other than that,
it'Ős just fucking beautiful.
I guess so.
I haven'Őt heard
anything in a while.
Maybe we should get him
down with the others.
Wait for the reinforcements
to find us.
That'Ős if anyone comes.
They don'Őt call this
Purple Heart Ridge for nothing.
Let'Ős get outta here.
What do you plan on doing
with that thing?
You ever see the
Babe hit one out
of Yankee stadium?
Dozens of times.
Are you good?
As long as there'Ős
a nice piece-of-shit cot
with someone else'Ős
blood smeared in it
waiting for me downstairs,
I'Őm ready for anything.
Then keep up. Come on.
Guess you don'Őt know
Jersey very well.
Hey, Doc.
Ted Williams, 127
home runs in five years.
You think he'Őll catch the Babe?
I think the Babe'Ős
record'Ős pretty safe.
Let'Ős see what we can do.
All right, clear the chamber!
Get out of there,
get out of the way,
come on!
Get my bag. Go get some
equipment, right now.
Come on. No, no, no, come on.
I could save you.
Yes, I can.
No, you can'Őt.
He hit the femoral artery.
It won'Őt take too long now.
Protect them.
No, no, no, no, no.
Vic, make sure my boy gets this.
He'Ős not old enough
to understand it yet,
but he will be.
He was a good man.
They'Őre gonna make it down here.
You know that.
It'Ős just a matter of time.
Then we'Őll keep fighting.
I'Őm gonna take the halls.
I'Őm gonna kill as many
of these guys as I can.
Anybody makes it down here,
it'Ős on you.
I'Őm coming with you.
If I don'Őt make it back here,
I want you to know
it'Ős been an honor.
Likewise.
You keep an eye on him.
Don'Őt worry.
Got him covered.
You good to hold fort
for me, Private?
Well, we'Őre in luck.
'ŐCause I just happened
to learn from the best.
Good whiskey.
Great whiskey, two bottles.
You just make it back.
You remember our bet, right?
You still think you can win?
You'Őre damn right.
Loser buys Dodger tickets.
Get the door.
Quiet.
Steady.
Shit.
This is the last one.
Make it count.
I'Őm out!
Good shot, kid.
That'Ős how we do it
in Paris, Texas.
Oh my god! Please, no!
Don'Őt die!
Come on, come on.
Don'Őt die.
You did good.
Is that it?
Is that all?
I'Őm sure there'Ős more coming.
I don'Őt think we could handle
another wave like that.
Is this everything
we had in the building?
As far as we know, yeah.
Goddamn.
We could use their ammo,
but that won'Őt last
the night.
Yeah.
That'Őll buy us some time, but that'Ős
not the solution.
So what now?
We just sit here and die?
Maybe we won'Őt have to.
I don'Őt think that'Ős enough.
It'Ős a flare gun.
Maybe we can get
some reinforcements.
Are you sure?
I'Őm out of other options.
Where are you gonna
do this? The roof?
No, I think I'Őd be
a target there.
Maybe around back.
Maybe there'Ős a little
clearing I can go to.
So you just gonna leave us?
Why don'Őt you just wait
till Porter gets back?
I don'Őt think
Porter'Ős coming back.
I'Őll be right back.
You know what'Ős out there.
A minefield.
If I'Őm not back in 20,
you get everybody you can.
You run like hell
until you find someone
friendly, okay?
Hopefully, it won'Őt
come to that.
How long has it been?
About two minutes.
That'Ős it?
Time goes by so slow
when there'Ős no gunfire.
Don'Őt worry.
He knows what he'Ős doing.
He can do it.
He talked me through
losing an arm.
He can make it
through a minefield.
Go!
Wait. There it is! He did it.
So it will be with
the resurrection of the dead.
The body that is sown
is perishable.
It is raised imperishable.
It is sown weak.
It is raised with power.
It is sown and dishonored,
is raised in glory.
It is sown as a natural body,
it rises as a spiritual body.
If there is a spiritual body,
there is a natural body.