I was dreaming
the day I met you
in 11th grade.
The dream of that dreamlike day.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I will call you again
when the bride has gotten the dress changed.
Excuse me.
Have you seen the bride's sisters?
Yes.
They've arrived here earlier.
I see.
Groom.
The bride wants to see you.
What's the matter?
I will finish changing soon.
Wait a moment there.
Oh, right. It seems they have come.
Seriously, what are they planning?
They have never changed since high school.
Problem girls.
I dreamed again just now.
How many times
will I see that day in my dreams?
Such a ridiculous nightmare
that is deeply engraved in my mind.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Am I still dreaming...
- I love you.
- Love you.
- Love. - I love you.
- I'm in love with you.
The Quintessential Quintuplets
(The Quintessential Quintuplets Movie)
The Movie
If you do not receive it,
Todo
If it doesn't get through.
Tsu
ta
wara
nai
no
na
ra
Kono kimochi mo warikirenai da ne
This feeling is also indivisible
Accelerate and move words
Kasoku
shite
ko
to
ba
wa
ugoku
tell me more
Mo
tto
takusan
oshi
ete yo
Hey, there's something I don't understand
koto
ga
koko
ni
aru
no
Hey,
Ki
mi
Ga
I love you, I won't lose to anyone.
Daisuki
nanda
I love you so much
Daisuki
nanda
dare
ni
mo
makenai
I won't loose to anyone.
dare
ni
mo
makenai
You even make me forget to breathe
Kokyuu sae mo wasurechau
I don't know if you'll be the only one
Kimi
wa
hitori
waka
nai
yo
This is the first time I feel something like this
Hajimete
datta
This is the first time
Hajimete
shitta
datta
kanjou
That I feel something like this
shitta
wa
kanjou
Your light is making me bloom
Hikari
wo
motome
saiteru
And how far does this love
Kono
koi
wa
Love
Koi
wa
Love
Koi
wa
Love
Koi
wa
will go I wonder?
Doko
made
tsuzuite
imasu ka?
(Here lies Nakano Family)
Yotsuba!
I got this!
Great!
Thanks to you girls,
it's another big victory today!
Especially Yotsuba!
Recently, you are making
a remarkable progress!
Eh, me?
Really?
We are quintuplets,
so it shouldn't be like that.
No. There is nothing wrong
with my judgment.
You should also follow Yotsuba's example
to practice hard.
Example?
Let's go now as the game has finished.
Or the store will close.
Why? Do you need to go shopping?
Yes! We want to buy mom a present!
Celebration of recovering from illness.
We five have saved our pocket money
for this day.
So, let's head for the florist!
Come on, Ichika you are so pushy.
Girls, let's go.
What kind of flowers will make mom happy
when she receives it as a present?
I heard that carnations
are suitable for a present to mom.
Carnations?
Yes. Although I don't know it clearly.
Yotsuba, how much do we have?
Well...
Eh? I might have lost the purse.
Have you found it there?
It doesn't seem to be here.
It was there before the soccer game.
It should be around here.
I'm looking for it deeper inside.
Yotsuba...
What should I do?
It's all my fault.
What should I do...
Sorry, girls.
It's all my fault.
It's not your fault, Yotsuba.
It would be lost
no matter who of us was keeping it.
Yes.
Because everyone's failure
will be divided into five equally.
Girls!
It probably can't be a substitute,
but I found a beautiful flower here.
This...
How about it?
Yotsuba, that is...
Sorry!
I'm just being self-serving.
We also found it.
- These flowers.
- We are really quintuplets.
I'm home.
Aren't you home?
Mom, congratulations!
We're glad you got well.
Look! These were collected by all of us!
Thank you for your hard work
today and always.
Thank you for always!
- Eh? Mom is frozen.
- Looks it's not enough...
For me,
Only if you five can grow up with health,
I couldn't be much happier.
Thank you all.
I think this is all.
Let's go back.
Could it be from dad?
No way.
The last summer vacation
of high school passed in a flash.
When the second semester begins,
we'll be busy preparing for
the school festival.
Ichika will be off school for a while, right?
Because I have started with the movie filming.
Is it okay with the number of attendance day?
Well, somehow.
Futarou said he would give me private lessons.
That being said...
I didn't expect we'd come back here.
(Notice of Demolition Work)
Demolition notice
Being evacuated half a year after we moved,
that's so unlucky of us.
Oh!
It's as tidy as usual!
It must be Ebata, right?
He might keep cleaning it all the time.
It definitely feels better in wider room.
Staff Room
(Staff Room)
Excuse me.
Ah, Itsuki.
What did you do in the staff room?
Something I can't understand
about today's class.
- I came to ask...
- I see!
I came for the school festival.
29th ASAHI SCHOOL FESTIVAL
The Sunrise
Fest
OCTOBER   (SAT) --   (MON)
(The 29th School Festival of Asahi Senior School)
Seems the class president
will take the lead in making all decisions.
(Sunrise Festival)
Eh? Class president means...
I wonder how Uesugi
would arrange this festival.
Anyway,
the third graders have a custom of stalls.
Fried chicken with Frankfurt.
Potato with butter is also good.
I'm sorry.
Save this topic for next time.
It's almost time for helping
in the cram school.
Hum. I thought Itsuki took eating
as the most important.
Everyone should have left...
Eh?
What's the matter, Yotsuba?
I'm sorry to interrupt
while you're studying.
Well...
Is it about the stalls
at the school festival?
Wait a moment.
I can't waste a second now.
Okay...
Raiha told me.
I have watched Ichika's commercial...
Don't forget it. It will be given in summer.
Vitamin Stimulus
(Vitamin Stimulation
METCH)
She's completely an actress.
She should have realized her dream.
Itsuki also wants to become a teacher.
It seems she has a dream
beyond her means.
- Yotsuba.
- Yes?
Do you have something
you want to become for the future?
Eh?
It's all of a sudden.
Well.
I haven't thought about it.
You have the outstanding physical ability.
You have a lot of choices in that direction.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's go around to get the information
about the stalls last year.
Huh.
But is it okay?
Uesugi, you said
you couldn't waste time...
That's why I'm doing so.
It's the last school event.
I won't waste any bit of it.
I've decided to enjoy it thoroughly
since I've chosen to do it.
The time is limited.
I could never have it enough.
I'll be counting on you.
Yes! Leave it to me!
(6. Rice cracker 5. Churro 4. Frankfurt)
(3. Fried chicken 2. Chocolate banana 1. Takoyaki)
This is the list of popular stalls last year.
If anyone who has ideas other than these,
1. Takoyaki
2. Choco-Bananas
3. Skewered Chicken
4. Sausages
5. Churros
6. Octopus Crackers
tell us any time you like.
I cast a vote for Takoyaki.
Let's stick to norms this way.
What's more, you have investigated
about this list, right?
If we go with Takoyaki, I will show you
my skills polished by my part-time job.
It sounds fun.
Anything else?
- Taiyaki!
- Bubble Tea!
Miku, do you have any idea?
Eh?
Pancake.
Well...
It's not in the data by last year.
But there can be.
Nice idea.
Miku, thank you.
I also think it's a good idea.
It will definitely look cute!
That's all for today. We'll discuss later.
Nakano.
Can we take part in the live stage?
Of course!
Clothing club offered this.
Will the customers come...
Wow! Amazing!
We can put a poster
in the designated place.
Please allow us to help you.
Thank you!
- Yotsuba is so popular.
- No, no.
Why is no one coming to me?
Popularity.
I want to send invitations to my relatives.
I have prepared!
Invitations...
Anyway, the stalls.
(Taiyaki, Bubble Tea, Pancake)
1. Takoyaki
2. Choco-Bananas
3. Skewered Chicken
4. Sausages
5. Churros
6. Octopus Crackers
Taiyaki
Bubble tea
Pancakes
(Taiyaki, Bubble Tea, Pancake)
No matter what we do,
I'm burning to try my hand at it.
Yes. I'm itching to show
what I can do.
Eh?
You want to be in charge of cooking?
There will be some customers
from outside too.
If you're not good at it,
you'll be food poisoning the local residents.
I'm getting better.
And you're there.
So I'm not worried.
O...Of course.
If you cook with me,
there is no chance of failure.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Good job.
Aren't you working a bit too hard?
Because it's the last event.
Let's make it a school festival
that will not leave any regrets.
Huh.
The last?
Futarou.
I'm glad that
you came specially to teach me.
But is it fine with your college entrance exam?
The preparation for school festival
also seems to be very busy...
Actually, today
I received the verdict
from my preferred school.
Eh?
Stop! Don't look!
Only this I don't want you to see!
Well, okay.
Seems going well.
(Grade: A) (Ranking 3rd out of 234516)
Grade
Rank
FUTAROU UESUGI
NINOMIYA UNIVERSITY
Rank III
Score
Obtained
Deviation
Value
(Grade: A) (Ranking 3rd out of 234516)
What! Boring.
I must say,
only you, Futarou
who is capable of study originally
could pull off something like that.
Please take care of everyone.
This is the crucial moment.
Don't worry.
Both their study and the school festival
will go well.
Wait and see, Ichika.
We will make it the best school festival.
Just give up, boys!
(Pancake, Takoyaki)
It's you girls who should give up!
Everyone likes fluffy pancakes so much!
Miku, say something too.
Well...
Look at last year's data!
There's no Japanese
who dislikes Takoyaki!
Right, Nino?
Well...
Didn't Nino said she likes pancake?
Why do you take her as on your side?
You were kidding, right, Nino?
Enough!
It can't be helped!
I am responsible for something
I proposed at the beginning.
Besides, eating and cooking are different.
That fluffy pancake,
even I could fail with it sometimes.
No further discussion is needed.
We have no choice but to do both!
I didn't expect the class would be
divided into halves because of that.
Yes. Why did you come out with pancake?
I heard that Futarou's mother
made pancakes often.
So,
then I recalled our mom.
Well, that's right.
That must be fluffy.
But it can't be made in a short time.
Have you ever made it?
That's the first dish
I challenged to make.
Takoyaki is much easier.
Especially so if it's a stall.
But you still didn't have to
say it so straightly...
I hate it. Something like
sneaking behind one's back.
Ah!
Nino, Miku.
You are together?
Futarou, what's the matter?
No, it's fine if so.
Well, you might be busy
for a lot of things.
But it's a long-awaited school festival.
So please enjoy yourselves.
What is he talking about?
I need to talk with Futarou.
- You go back first.
- Miku.
Futarou.
What's up, Miku?
Before the school festival,
there's something I need to tell you.
I see.
I also have something to tell you.
You can go first.
Okay. I heard it. Miku...
Your grade of the college entrance exam
seems to be A.
You did a really nice job!
Thinking about it,
it's been really a long way.
But all will be rewarded
once you enroll in college.
And it'll be worth it
for all the tutoring I've done.
That's right...
Well, Futarou.
Date with me.
Ah, sorry!
I didn't mean something strange.
Next Sunday,
can you go out with me?
Huh?
Eh?
Nino, you're also going home now?
Yes.
I am looking for someone
coming home with me.
Really?
But sorry.
I am going to the cram school directly.
Ah, I see.
You take it so seriously.
Ah, that...
How about your grade
in the college entrance exam, Nino?
It's not as bad as I thought.
It's B.
What?
What should I do, Nino?
I had been working on it
with all my strength.
(Grade D)
But this result!
Grade
NAKANO ITSUKI
NAME
UNIVERSITY OF
EDUCATIONAL PSYCHOLOGY
(Grade D)
There's no hope for my future!
After all I'm just a parody of my mom!
Becoming a teacher
is further than a dream!
Calm down!
Excuse me for being distraught.
The teacher said
it's better to have a talk with parents.
But something like that...
Our parents aren't there for us to talk to.
No, I didn't mean that.
I don't want to worry dad anymore.
Huh? Worry?
When did that man...
It's all thanks to dad
that we can grow up until now.
I gradually started to think that way.
Those flowers must be from dad.
Although he hasn't had much things done directly,
I think he's always been concerned about us.
That's not...
For now, I'll have a talk with Shimoda.
I will try to have a talk with the teacher
who takes care of me in the cram school.
(Akaya Academy)
And recently,
there'll be a special lecture
held by a famous teacher.
(Overwhelming teaching ability!
Thorough leadership!)
BY Mr. HINOSUKE MUDOU
Special Lecture
(Mr. Mudo Jinnosuke)
(Special Lecture)
Nino!
I have prepared
the invitation mentioned before.
I don't need it anymore.
- Eh, is it okay?
- Something like inviting dad
just came up in a thoughtless moment.
I think it's a good idea...
Anyway, I guess he won't come...
Even at home we can barely see him.
He's always doing something
behind our back.
So harsh...
But... Oh!
The girls who stared at me.
Before it gets troublesome,
I will just avoid it.
I have known about your ideas.
Eh?
In conclusion,
It's weird that Nino stays among boys.
You tried to claim that she must be
aiming at one boy
by cast amorous glances.
That's right!
If her target is Yusuke...
With Nino being our opponent,
We have no chance to win.
Sakura.
Cheer up!
That's wrong.
Eh?
The one Nino likes
is not someone in favor of Takoyaki.
At least I can confirm that.
So don't worry.
I don't believe it!
Why do you know that, Uesugi?
Because the class president
is in a neutral position
and couldn't vote for either side.
Huh? I don't understand!
It doesn't matter!
Yes! That's right!
Because Nino...
Likes me!
So
just make up.
U...Uesugi.
Could you stop daydreaming?
Nino is pitiful this way.
No! She really...
I don't think it's bad
to do something behind one's back.
He must got his reasons.
Yotsuba.
About the invitation,
let's think about the contents together.
I don't remember allowing you to enter.
Get out now, Uesugi.
Hey, that's too aloof of you.
I came to inform you of some good news.
He's coming.
After more than ten years.
(Overwhelming teaching ability!
Thorough leadership!)
(Mr. Mudo Jinnosuke)
(Special Lecture)
This is Anne.
The one behind is
Sun!
Well, a question for everyone.
What's the name of this cute babe?
Don't they all look the same?
I can't tell the differences.
I want to have a guess.
Correct!
It's natural that they're similar.
These five penguins are sisters.
Just like you five.
Now that you say that,
that one is similar to Nino.
Then is that one Miku?
Futarou...
Futarou.
I want to learn about cooking.
So I don't want to go to college.
Sorry, Futarou.
I see.
I will support it if you have decided.
You have a very complicated face.
That's right. Technical school...
There's also something like that.
I also think there's nothing wrong
to go to college.
I don't know what the correct answer is.
But...
I can't help but want
to move on to my dream.
That's what I wanted to tell you.
Because you are special to me, Futarou.
That means...
Of course, something strange.
Why did Miku say that at such a time?
It shouldn't be just about her future.
I have said it.
Then it's your turn next time, Futarou.
The thing I must say out is...
Welcome home, brother.
Why are you in my home?
Here you are.
Yotsuba said she didn't remember
she has given it to you.
Ah...Thanks...
Alright!
The curry is ready.
May I have some?
Is it okay for you to do so?
I have heard about your grade.
Even though, I won't give up on
my desired school.
I will do my best with the determination
of skipping school festival.
Please see to it.
I'll feel upset if you get rejected.
If you fail like this, all I have done
would be meaningless.
That's wrong.
Ichika who dreams to become an actress.
Miku who aims at a chef.
Is your time spent with them also meaningless?
I don't want to think so.
Our relationships can no longer
be described as
just a tutor and students.
Uesugi.
Even if in the future,
failures would be waiting.
If we hadn't come to this school...
Would we regret
not having met you?
The relationship...
Was not meaningless.
The next,
it's my turn.
Come to the class room,
(The First Day of the School Festival)
(Planetarium)
Planetarium
Attention, please.
Please gather in the gym.
at 3 P.M
(At 15:00 o'clock)
(The 29th Sunrise Festival)
The opening ceremony of the 29th
Sunrise Festival of Asahi Senior School
will now begin!
(15:00 o'clock in the first day of
the school festival, come to the classroom)
Come to the class room,
on the first day of the school festival
at 3 P.M
(Mail Sending)
Sending message
(Mail transmitted.)
Message sent.
First of all, here comes
what our school is proud of,
the opening act by the female student unit!
♪Love vacation. When you are in love♪
Rabu
☆
bakeeshon
koi
ni
yasumi
Rabu
bakeeshon
Nante
mono
yasumi
♪There's no break♪
m
o
n
Nante
a
i
mono
n
o
nai
Futari
dake
no
tokubetsu
♪The special one for only us two♪
d
a
k
e
Futari
n
o
dake
(Sunrise Festival)
♪The special one for only us two♪
n
a
…
tokubetsu
Keep
♪The special one for only us two♪
Out
Line!?
Yeah
Yeah!!
na…
♪Keep out line! Yeah! Yeah!♪
Keep
Line!?
Yeah
Rabu
☆
bakeeshon
kono
kimochi
♪Love vacation, this feeling♪
R
a
b
u
Yeah!!
☆
Rabu
bakeeshon
kono
Datte
mou
tomannai
kimochi
♪Cannot be stopped anymore♪
Nino is so amazing!
m
o
u
Datte
She really participated.
♪Cannot be stopped anymore♪
Oshite
hiite
naichatte...
n
o
tomannai
♪Push, pull and cry♪
h
i
t
e
Oshite
hiite
koi
n
o
bakeeshon!
♪The love vocation♪
naichatte...
bakeeshon!
Nino!
(Corn Dog, Crepes, Tropical Juice, Marshmallow...)
The 29th Sunrise Festival
(Bite-sized Sponge Cakes, Target Shooting)
begins!
(Maids Cafe)
(The 29th School Festival of Asahi Senior School
Sunrise Festival)
Miku, it tastes so good!
Who did you learn from?
Learned through part-time job.
Here come customers.
(Pancake, Egg Senbei)
Thank you for your patronage.
Could she stay calm until 15 o'clock?
Good!
All the inspections have been gone through.
Ah, Yotsuba.
Oh, she's the red!
Your opening dance
was so cute!
- I have become your fan!
- Please have my corn dog if you like.
Thanks.
I was willing to see how the stall was doing.
Maybe Ichika is always in this feeling...
Nino!
What... It's Itsuki.
That was really a charming dance!
I even didn't feel like
it's just during a school festival.
What are you doing
as it's now the school festival?
I will end it before 15:00 o'clock.
Don't worry.
I'm tired.
Where is Fu?
This way please.
Thanks for the guidance.
You are a great young man.
Uesugi!
Eh?
I want to make it a resting place here,
but what should I do?
Ah...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Miku, good job.
So slow, you are late.
Anyway,
everyone is here now.
No, one else left.
- Yo!
- Ichika!
You came!
Why didn't you contact us?
I'm glad no chaos have been caused.
I managed it.
Now we can say everyone is here.
After all, this makes my calm down.
That's right.
It's a rare chance, so just enjoy!
We bought a lot at the stalls!
I have been enduring!
It looks so delicious!
I like all of you five.
It's such a sudden.
W...What do you mean?
I hope all we six can
keep the current relations forever.
But...
I think I have to give an answer.
Futarou.
It's fine.
Really?
Anyways, it's not like I'm so unsophisticated
that I must bring this up
during the school festival.
It's just that...
I also have something
I haven't sorted out.
Give me more time until the last day.
Come on, what's that?
That sounds so discouraging.
Then let's pull together again
and have a toast!
I want orange juice!
May I have a matcha soda?
We don't have that.
Finally...
You said it out.
Until you figure out this difficult question,
it will take a lot of time.
Don't tease me, please.
But, I am so jealous.
This is yours, Futarou.
Oh.
So,
celebrating the successful end of
the first day of school festival...
Cheers!
Everyone,
the second day of Sunrise Festival!
(Sunrise Festival)
Let's have an unscheduled interview with
the customers here today.
(Sunrise Festival)
Is Nakano watching?
Do you remember me?
I come to see you.
Are you still running?
Please give back the micro!
Sorry for the impoliteness.
What...
Well, let's start over.
Hi, miss!
What are you here for?
Me?
I come to meet a childhood friend.
Uesugi, you don't have job today.
(Sunrise Festival)
Eh?
It's a rare chance.
(Corn)
Just enjoy the school festival.
I don't have the money to
have fun or eat...
Right, maybe I can go there...
Ah, I found you.
Futarou!
You have grown up!
Takebayashi!
(Target Shooting, Bite-sized Sponge Cakes,
Grilled Rice Balls)
(Target Shooting)
Futarou you are so clumsy.
You should make it a little more left.
You are so annoying by my side.
I want that one!
Aim that next time!
He said that to us yesterday,
but is dating another girl today?
Uesugi is not to be sneezed at.
Futarou, come here.
Hey!
Ah!
(Fluffy Pancake)
Would you like a piece of pancake?
Futarou.
There's pancake!
I want to eat!
Ah...
This is the stall of my class.
Fu...
Thanks for taking care of my Futarou.
My?
Who are you?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Takebayashi.
We have been in the same grade
from primary school.
Oh, is that so?
We are also in the same grade.
And also tutor and students.
So it can be said we are much closer
than just classmates.
Really! It's an coincidence!
I have also taught Futarou once!
I was surprised
when I was asked for tutoring by him
a problem child who listened to none.
No, they are my students.
Ah, really?
It's clear then.
You and I,
whose relationship to him is closer?
Yotsuba,
I'm already...
Uesugi and I...
Thanks.
If that's true,
it can be said that we had been
indirectly taken care by you.
It seems the time we spent with Uesugi
has lost to you.
But,
we won't lose in terms of the depth.
You girls...
It's so shameful, so please stop.
Eh!
Besides, Takebayashi...
Stop teasing please.
They are my rare friends.
They are all special.
Ah!
You really have grown up.
I apologize to both of you.
May I have one pancake?
Yes!
Yotsuba...
Sorry.
I have to go back to work.
Fu!
My feeling has never changed!
Welcome back. What happened?
Futarou looks good.
All the quintuplets are nice girls.
Eh? Quintuplets?
Just do your best,
Futarou.
Is this choice...
Or,
is choosing itself right?
To figure that question out,
three days
are too short.
(When the last festival comes to Ichika)
The Last Festival - Ichika's Side
Until now,
(When the last festival comes to Ichika)
School Festival of Asahi Senior School,
closing party,
and all schedules are over.
(The First Day of the School Festival)
First day of the school Festival
The taxi is so slow...
- Well...
- It reminds me
Nakano Ichika
seems to be in the school.
Nakano Ichika!
She is so cute in the previous movies.
Ah!
I also want to kiss Ichika like a drama!
Maybe, are you shocked that I kissed?
No.
I am an actress.
I need to do so sometime.
I don't mean that.
That's right.
Futarou has experienced that, right?
Why did you...
And that's just an accident.
You really have kissed!
So, with who?
I... I don't know.
You all dressed like Itsuki at that time.
So, who do you think it was?
The taxi comes!
You had a narrow escape.
Well...
Maybe I won't be able to come to
the school festival for the next few days.
So can't you answer me now?
Well if you are still wondering...
Got it.
I can't choose anyone.
That's my answer.
The worst!
You are always saying honeyed words!
(The Second Day of the School Festival)
Second day of the school festival
It hurts!
(The Second Day of the School Festival)
Okay! Good.
That settles!
A...Are you okay?
Ichika, you seems familiar with
hitting people.
Ah!
I worked hard today too!
Go back to hotel and have a nice sleep.
Ichika, something terrible!
Boss?
There was a call that...
Your sister seemed to have fallen down.
I am relieved as it seems you're fine.
Take a nice rest.
Eh?
Nino, Futarou...
Ichika, you also came.
I got a call.
So I can't contain myself.
What about the others?
They have calmed down temporarily.
We are all fine,
so don't worry about us.
I see... That's great.
The clean-up has not finished,
so I'm back to school.
Fu, please send Ichika back.
Well...
So, I'll go home today.
Have you done your work today, Futarou?
Well...
Then, let's have a walk.
Wow!
It's unexpectedly wide here.
Futarou, do you remember?
Isn't here the venue of
the fireworks display?
With no stalls or humans,
it's wide indeed.
I didn't mean without any people.
Do you know?
There are a lot of couples formed
in these three days.
Among the tree days,
what makes the most couples is
the closing party at the third day.
I wondered if you knew it
and said that.
Do you think I'm someone who
swims with the tide?
You're talking like that again.
You look tough but sometimes
you're unexpectedly vulgar.
Huh? When?
When you saw a luxury car,
you peeked into it.
When you went on a long-awaited trip,
you were so excited.
When you were at the top of the hill,
you yelled yoo-hoo.
You have a good memory.
Well,
those are also moments
when you are so cute.
Please cherish such sincere feelings.
So,
don't say you can't choose anyone.
I myself can't understand my feelings.
You have taken it too difficult
and overthought too much.
Or just try not to think.
We talked about kiss yesterday, right?
Nino, Miku, Yotsuba and Itsuki.
I have a question.
Who will make you be pleased with?
What?
Ah, a vending machine!
I'll give you money,
so buy whatever you like.
Huh?
Whatever you want to drink.
I will wait for you at the bench there.
Why suddenly...
Futarou!
Nino is black tea.
Miku is green tea.
Yotsuba is juice.
Itsuki is coffee!
So cunning...
I have to do this.
So what will you do, Futarou?
(Ten Minutes Later)
Ten Minutes Later
Mon...
I kept her waiting too long.
I have showed something wack of myself.
I always feel like that when with you.
The first son to the first daughter...
We have both been so hard.
Eh?
You looked at them, right?
My lips.
Why?
Were you awake?
Why did you look at them?
Who is the one I kissed
among you five,
I was thinking it might be you.
I'm so disgusting.
Disgusting.
Ah!
How about it? Was it me?
I...Ichika.
So rather than just seeing, isn't it easier
to tell the difference by doing it actually?
I... I know, but...
Do it merely for that?
You may have used to it in acting.
Oh...
The drama mentioned yesterday,
the partner was also an actress.
Eh?
Something like missing a male...
I'm still NG with it.
So, you are the first...
It's not something
you can easily do with a girl
in same grade.
So remember it.
Ah, I forgot to ask.
Did you feel happy?
What's that?
Why you talked so condescendingly?
Cherish your sincere feelings.
Come on, you are shy?
Well.
That's right.
No matter who will Futarou choose.
This feeling,
doesn't seem to last for much longer.
(When the last festival comes to Nino)
The Last Festival - Nino's Side
Until now,
(When the last festival comes to Nino)
School Festival of Asahi Senior School,
closing party,
and all schedules are over.
(The First Day of the School Festival)
So, celebrating the successful end of
First day of the School festival
the first day of school festival...
Cheers!
Great!
Hey you!
Delicious!
How? How about it?
You...
How long will you
keep this showy costume?
But, I wanted to show you.
Nino, you was so cute!
Uh-huh...
It was me
who should have taken part in that
opening ceremony.
Nino helped me to participate!
You have had a nice face to anyone
and accept too much work!
Don't you also help in the theater club?
Stop before the limit comes!
Nino, you still always
take care of your sisters.
Not only because of that.
I took this work because...
I thought I could have a good overall view
of all the audience seats from the stage.
What does it mean?
We...
Sent an invitation to dad.
He didn't show up at all.
Well, I didn't expect him
to come at the beginning.
I don't mind.
I see...
Maybe he has come now.
Let's have a look around the stalls.
Gah! He's not here.
Wasn't there any contact?
Eh? No!
Come on!
With such a bold confession,
why can we be alone?
Just contact him directly.
Stop!
Enough.
I haven't been expecting from the beginning.
Didn't you gather your courage
and send the invitation?
Can you accept it?
I'll believe and wait.
(The Second Day of the School Festival)
Second day of the School Festival
(Bubble Tea)
Fluffy and sweet pancakes.
Would you like some?
Miss. Pancake seller.
There are obviously more people
than yesterday.
It seems it's been rumored to come here.
Hi!
Uesugi contacted us.
Is this store Nino's class'?
Good afternoon.
Manager, thanks for coming.
Eh, didn't you feel disappointed just now?
(Fluffy Pancake)
I thought it was dad for a second.
Everyone, good job!
The second day of School Festival of
Asahi Senior School is over now.
Hey, hey.
We might win the best store!
I can't wait longer.
Eh?
Nino, come with me.
Uesugi?
It's fine.
I won't come.
I sent an invitation, but dad didn't come.
We are no more than dusts for him.
Although the school festival
will go on tomorrow,
it's already enough.
It won't come true anyway,
I just regret that I tried to invite him.
I don't know well about your family.
I only know it's different from
the usual parent-child relationship.
But on the contrary, do you know this?
He shows extreme cautiousness to me.
Huh?
Should I call
that the eye expression of a father?
But I know, if he didn't love you, he could
never have made that eye expression to me.
That's why he was complaining.
He said you were so troublesome.
Hey, Uesugi!
We found the people you showed us!
We saw the video again.
And wondered if there's someone with
the same characters you've been looking for.
Where do you come from today?
Oh, a call from my company?
Sorry for the impoliteness.
What!
How? It's just like this...
Thank you.
It seems he has come.
What to do, Nino?
Fu,
take me to dad's.
That's right.
Why did I become discouraged?
Regardless of pushing,
pulling or no response...
Now I shall go confront him.
(General Hospital)
(Admission Pass)
Hi.
I came to give back your daughter I have borrowed.
Today why did you...
Go home before it gets dark.
Wait. It will be ready in a while.
Have a try please.
We have known you came to school today.
Pancake?
It's surprisingly cheap to make.
And my daughters were so happy
to have some.
I wanted to make it for them
for the last time...
The last time...
There's nothing like that.
Nakano.
I can't express my gratitude more.
But
don't spend your precious time
on me with little remaining days anymore.
Remaining days...
Please don't say such a thing.
Doctor Reina is my teacher.
Teacher.
That's something years ago.
Besides, if you die,
your daughters will be so sad.
That's right.
I only feel regretful about them.
Making sure their grown-up safe and happy
is my responsibility.
Thank you, Nakano.
Please let me be spoiled by
your grace a little longer.
When I'm discharged,
please let me treat you a meal.
Pancake.
I think you will like it too.
The dough was made by Miku.
She who is bad at cooking,
has found her goal
and been doing her best.
Not only Miku.
All five of us,
have grown much more mature than the past.
We want you to see that growth by our sides.
Dad.
You ate it!
Eh... But...
Why are you putting on that face?
This taste...
You have faced it without running away.
Eh? What do you mean?
Besides, there're too many.
I can't finish them all by myself.
Let's eat it with the whole family next time.
What are you saying suddenly!
But, everyone...
Will be very happy.
Great, Nino.
Then, can I use the toilet.
Uesugi,
wait.
Is this your plan?
No?
Yes. He just took me here.
So what?
That's still not something a tutor should do.
But that's something I can't do.
I think it's good to have asked you
to take care of them sincerely from my heart.
Oops!
As an abortive parent,
I hope you can think about
your relationship with my daughters carefully.
Fu, thank you for today.
And for all until now...
And... besides that...
About tomorrow...
Hey! Danger!
That was close!
Huh?
What are you doing?
I just slipped.
We are going back.
Tsk, so pitiful.
Well. It's fine like so.
Barely safe.
Are you okay?
After all I must attack ahead for love.
Eh?
What again?
Ugh!
Hey, dad.
I just want to tell you this.
No matter how the relationship between
our sisters will change in the future,
my feeling will never change.
Asking Fu to be our tutor,
thank you.
The Last Festival - Miku's side
(When the last festival comes to Miku)
Until now,
School Festival of Asahi Senior School,
closing party,
and all schedules are over.
(The First Day of the School Festival)
Primer día del festival.
Eh, isn't he from our class?
He's checking our selling situation.
Just because we compromised.
We can't lose to the boys' Takoyaki!
Let's work harder, Miku!
W...Well.
About the boys in our class...
Let's stop being stubborn
and make up with them!
It must be fun to work together!
If only I have the courage to say so...
Huh?
He's not here.
I will try to look there.
Hey, Uesugi!
Huh?
Tell the boys!
Stop reconnoitering sneakily.
Or rather, you guys could make up.
Well,
Maybe I can...
go check their selling too?
Tomorrow is crucial!
We can't lose to the girls!
Yay!
What should I do, Futarou?
If there's someone
who can make a change,
MIku, only you.
As you are in the opposing side,
maybe you can change their minds.
Well, it's only my intuition.
You're free to
decide whether to believe.
Uh-huh, I believe Futarou.
Good afternoon.
Nakano...
Nakano!?
Why are you here,
the leader of pancake?
W...Well...
Takoyaki,
please give me one!
Huh?
It looks delicious.
I'll enjoy having it.
Be careful as it's hot.
Thank you.
Delicious!
I want the girls of our class
to have a try too.
Huh?
After the end of the first day,
I will take everyone here.
You boys' seriousness
should be transmitted to everyone!
It's all of a sudden for you to say that...
They said something like Takoyaki sucked!
We won't make Takoyaki for them.
Hey, you should accept...
Wait, Futarou.
I believe it...
If I don't say it...
I'm sorry they said so that day.
But,
I believe you also don't want
the festival to end in this way.
Let's make it a great school festival that
could delight everyone,
even after all is over and we get graduated.
Speaking of that,
Maeda, you give some to Matsui to eat, right?
Boo! I told you to not say out.
What did you do, Maeda...
Only you stole the march,
I also wanted Maruyama to have a try!
Then I want Yuri to try!
Come on.
Well, it's not that I don't have someone
who I want to her to eat.
Nakano...
For these guys too,
could I ask you to bring the girls?
Uh-huh, of course.
Thank you. It's all because of Futarou.
Huh? I didn't do anything.
It's you who moved everyone.
You become stronger, Miku.
Class 1 Grade 3,
the stall of Takoyaki
is decided to be closed.
(The Second Day of the School Festival)
The Sunrise festival
Second day of the School Festival
Miku, I've found Uesugi.
He's really outside.
He's talking with an unknown girl!
Eh!
Do you know her?
No.
Could it be...
Uesugi said so yesterday.
He said...
He likes all five of us.
Let's trust Uesugi!
Trust.
When we just met,
he told me...
To trust the thing I like.
No matter what happens,
I like Futarou.
Because I like Futarou.
I will trust him and go ahead.
(The Third Day of the School Festival)
Third day of the school festival
Miku?
I haven't seen you for the whole day.
Sorry about the class stall...
Futarou.
Come with me.
Roof?
Isn't it prohibited during the school festival?
Uh-huh. I don't think
it'll cause any troubles here.
Stop the nonsense!
Anyway, you're laughing at the fact that
we can't open the store anymore!
I said no one said so!
It's bad of you boys to cause the accident!
What the heck!
What?
Was it you who called them here?
It's true it won't make any trouble here.
That's wrong.
It's me who made the trouble.
Nakano.
Miku, what is the letter about?
Make up.
Eh?
Please! Make! Up!
All the boys and girls
are stubborn all the time.
We are already senior school students!
We will be in college next year.
Don't you feel shamed to
quarrel like children like this?
There shouldn't be any better or worse
between pancakes and Takoyaki.
Of course the same for boys and girls.
Both are delicious.
All have worked hard!
Why can't you admit that?
School festival
was not fun from the preparation.
I felt uncomfortable.
I have been enduring.
It's the limit now!
Miku...
You...
The girls have been working and are tired.
I hope the boys could help with
the operation of the pancake stall.
Huh?
No, but...
Even if I'd agree,
what would the others say?
Leave it to me.
I will persuade them.
Trust me.
Sorry.
I thought it's impossible
for them to make up.
So I drew the line
and gave up by myself causally.
You really gave me a lesson.
Eh?
Miku?
Who was that girl?
Girl?
The girl you did target shooting with.
She's a childhood friend.
Do you like her? As a female.
J...Just a friend.
Really? Then it's fine.
I have been enduring to not ask about it.
Enduring, why...
Just ask me without consideration.
Eh?
Uh-huh. I knew.
So,
I want to kiss you.
Eh?
Although I said without consideration,
why is what coming now?
Sorry, I will listen to your answer later.
No matter what insurmountable wall appears,
as long as I trust myself,
I can go ahead towards anywhere.
No more hesitation.
The Last Festival - Yotsuba's Side
(When the last festival comes to Yotsuba)
Until now,
School Festival of Asahi Senior School,
closing party,
and all schedules are over.
(The First Day of School Festival)
First day of the School Festival
Thank you!
(Theater Club Performance Venue)
Queen Emerald!
This is the end, heroes.
It's pitiful of you to die here.
Become my subordinates!
I wondered how about the show at 1.
I'm glad that Senior Nanako
could take my part.
I'm also glad that
I can help.
I come for the security check.
Thanks for your hard work.
Freshness of ingredients
seems to be no problem.
Ah.
The paper trash there
is very dangerous.
Please put it away.
If it goes on like this,
I can make it by 15:00 o'clock.
How about the fried chicken?
Thank you for coming to help.
Please take these service tickets.
(Fried Chicken Free Treat)
I have been longing to eat!
This is... my limit...
You worked really hard.
Yotsuba...
Uesugi, you're as weak as a bean sprout.
So please take a rest.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine now.
Excuse me.
I want to finish it before 15:00 o'clock.
I'm worried about you.
You can't move
before you listen to my words.
It reminds I haven't eaten anything
from morning...
There are so many stalls!
That's why you have no power.
This is for you.
Please have a full meal.
Eh?
Is it okay?
Yes! I'm full.
I'm full and good!
Let's carry it and go!
Yotsuba,
thank you.
It's fine to have you with me.
What are you saying?
It's just helping each other.
The same for me...
Only by being approved by Uesugi,
I feel that all is rewarded.
Two days left
before Uesugi giving the answer.
It'll be another day like today.
I'm sure so.
But,
if he were to choose me...
Damn!
Second day of the School Festival
(The Second Day of School Festival)
Why?
Being decided to be closed...
We worked hard just for this day.
Considering such an accident happened,
we can only accept it.
We were told to be careful
as it was dangerous, didn't we?
Damn!
Please give me some work!
Huh?
Is there something troubling you?
Ah, here are you.
You are a friend of Futarou, right?
Eh?
School or at home?
It's the hospital.
I was shocked
when I heard you were here.
You didn't give yourself any time to rest, right?
I see.
Sorry to worry you.
I will go back now.
There are still lots of things to do.
Eh?
If I don't hurry up,
everyone in theater club will feel troubled.
Yotsuba, it's already night.
(General Hospital)
The second day has been over.
Six years ago in Kyoto,
was it you who met Futarou?
Why...
After that,
he showed me the photo so much that
I started to hate it.
I asked your sisters
at the pancake stall just now,
and I knew you got separated alone that day.
I can see why you could be his teacher now.
I'm glad he could meet you.
I will tell Futarou about this...
Please don't say!
Why?
Because I don't want to disappoint him.
Uesugi has been striving on a right path.
But I was obsessed with useless things
and spent the six years meaninglessly.
I was useless to anyone,
and have only made troubles.
What is the meaning of my existence?
Only this?
You think you are someone
meaningless and unnecessary.
I know someone who said the same words.
And that person now
is looking forward and starting to go ahead.
May you also step out from the past.
You got up?
Uesugi...
Let me through please.
If I don't go.
What will you do if you go?
Everyone has already gone home.
Then I will go apologize
to every one of them.
Not only everyone in theater club.
But also those who I took quests from afterwards.
Those I made troubles to...
I'm to blame.
What should I say to them?
But I can't let you go.
It's said you need to
stay absolutely rested until tomorrow.
I'm not going to leave here.
Have a seat for now.
I will tell you.
About what happened during the school festival
when you were not there.
This is the end,
heroes!
This girl!
She's the leader of
the track-and-field sports club, isn't she?
She wanted to meet you.
Seems she was there
at yesterday's performance.
But the size of the costume
was taken of me.
Do you remember them two?
They are from the clothing club.
Could it be...
Did they sew the costume?
I'm to blame.
Not only them two...
(Reception This Way)
(Fried Chicken)
Did you notice?
It's not blamed on you.
All gathered for you.
It's helping each other, right?
Sometimes you can be the one to be helped.
Please entrust us.
I'm also the one who owned you a favor.
Uesugi,
for the inconvenience I caused this time,
I apologize sincerely.
The last day...
Please take
my position at the festival.
Ah, all on me.
Third day of the School Festival
(The Third Day of the School Festival)
Uesugi Futarou.
Long time no see, Reina...
I had so many things to do today
and I'm tired now.
Please come to me later.
Thanks for remembering
and keeping the promise.
I didn't keep it.
Sorry.
Never mind.
Doesn't Futarou care?
Well...
What is much more important than
something in the past
is the present.
Ah.
I won't rely on the memories with you anymore.
I will go to find my own value on my own.
So,
this is the end.
I had a really shameful dream.
Might be because too many things happened
during the school festival.
It's so daring for me!
He will forgive me.
The last time we create
some memories together.
It's not the time for me
to cling to the old days.
With this,
I feel like I can move forward too.
I also...
(When the last festival comes to Yotsuba)
The Last Festival - Itsuki's Side
Until now,
(When the last festival comes to Yotsuba)
School Festival of Asahi Senior School,
closing party,
and all schedules are over.
(The First Day of the School Festival)
First day of the School Festival
You are...
(Overwhelming teaching ability!
Thorough leadership!)
BY Mr. HINOSUKE MUDOU
Special Lecture
(Mr. Mudo Jinnosuke)
(Special Lecture)
Thanks for your instruction
at that time, Mr. Mudo.
Wonderful!
How stoic you are to study
during such a festival.
Well...
Well, I want to go to college
and become a teacher.
The same path as my mother I longed for.
My mom was also a teacher.
I knew.
Eh?
I was her homeroom teacher.
You look exactly the same as
your mother when she was young.
Exactly the same...
Yes, to some distorted extent.
She was admiring me
and went on to a teaching job
that didn't suit her.
She's been regretting that until the end.
My life
was full of mistakes.
If you simply just want to
step the path of your mom,
then I don't recommend it.
Brother,
was there really a fire at the stall?
Ah.
No one was hurt though.
That's the most important.
By the way, Futarou.
Didn't you see a strange old man
during the school festival?
Eh?
That's right.
Dad has been saying about him
all the time today.
It's fine if you didn't see him.
Like this, his beard is thick.
Ah!
You mean the one whose face would be
more like a normal face if it's turned upside down?
He really came.
Who is that old man?
Maybe I should have told you...
(The Second Day of the School Festival)
Second day of the school festival
That man is...
What's the matter?
I kept considering when to confide in you.
You mother was my former student.
And my former colleague.
And...
My ex-wife.
Which means, I am
your father.
Father?
I was hoping to meet you.
I was traveling around the country
while thinking of you girls
at somewhere I didn't know.
Once
I saw Ichika on TV.
Then I realized now is the time
I take the responsibility as a father.
Why now!
I heard about you from mom.
As soon as you found out
that mom was having a quintuplet,
you disappeared!
At that time,
what was mom feeling like?
To you, I...
Sorry!
Please let me atone for my sins.
Even from now,
I want to do anything I can
to my daughters as a father.
Don't get involved with us anymore.
We already have a father.
Is it Nakano?
When your mother died,
what did he do to you?
He lets the daughters keep chasing
the shadow of their dead mom,
and step into the same wrong way with your mom.
Being a teacher is not suitable for you.
You should know it the best.
I can't pretermit it as your father.
My love towards you all
drives me to do so!
Itsuki?
Yes.
How can I say?
Is she the same as usual?
I haven't seen her from yesterday,
so I don't know.
What's the matter?
I suspect that your biological father
has contacted Itsuki.
Are you kidding?
Why?
Third day of the School Festival
(The Third Day of the School Festival)
Itsuki hasn't come yet.
It is the last day today.
What's the matter?
She's been keeping herself
inside her room since yesterday.
I see.
Wait.
Eh?
Are you going for Itsuki?
Take this.
Is it okay?
That's why you are Fu.
You enjoy doing such things.
I entrust you with her.
Pleas take care of Itsuki.
You...
Uesugi...
Although I know it's meaningless,
why am I still doing this?
Don't mind about that old man.
He thought he said appreciate words anyway
but it's wrong...
Mom also said the same.
Itsuki...
You must no be like me.
Even though I still can't give up.
I've been taking my mom as
my goal all the time.
Am I wrong having
a dream like that?
It may be true.
It could be no good to become a teacher.
It will make you realize that
not only excellent students,
in the whole world,
there are also some unimaginable idiots.
(Be cuter in smooth photos)
You'll still have to follow up them
even if it means to alter your principles.
There is no doubt
that getting involved with others
will make you tired
both physically and mentally.
(Biological defense mechanism by barrier)
Among them,
there may also be some rebellious students.
Even before them, you can't escape,
and have to continue to face it.
It's really a hard work.
I have had enough of it.
I will never become a teacher.
But so what?
It's worthless to listen to
others' playful words.
It's your own dream!
No matter how adverse it is,
it's you who decide
whether to go ahead or give up.
Is it really my dream?
I just want to become someone like mom.
Before,
I've been told by someone.
Pursuing your dream
while aiming for your mom
is totally different from following
your mom's steps while aiming for your dream.
If you can understand it,
admiring and aiming for your parents
are definitely nothing wrong.
I...
I want to become a teacher like my mom!
On my own will,
I am aiming for mom!
If my student wishes so,
as a tutor, I have only one thing I can do.
To support you with whole heart.
Only that.
Uesugi.
I came up with something good.
Please help me with my study.
Of course.
Thank you.
But, before that...
(Chicken Steak)
I have got something I have to do.
Good afternoon, Mr. Mudo.
Hi!
I didn't expect Itsuki you,
out of the five girls, would come to me first.
You started to listen to your father's words.
Is it okay to say that?
Father? Stop joking!
You are...
Oops! Mr. Mudo, long time no see.
Although,
looks like we're not the ones
who have a need here.
Mr. Mudo.
You look good.
Nakano...
It's good to have a chance to
apologize to you.
Because I've caused you
so much trouble.
I am sorry.
No.
I am thankful to you.
Huh?
It's your irresponsibility
that brought my daughters and me together.
I'm not sure about that.
Regarding responsibility,
you don't seem to be able to take it either.
That's why Itsuki came here by herself.
Not to you who is unreliable,
but came to me.
Itsuki is here?
What are you talking about?
Look carefully.
Itsuki is not here.
Huh?
I'm here.
What's your purpose?
Sorry to deceive you.
But I knew it would turn out like this.
So what?
I just took you wrong.
If there's love,
he could have distinguished us.
That's what mom said.
Her words again!
Enough!
That casual nonsense.
How long will you keep believing?!
Forget it now!
She should say this as a mother.
Try to remember.
What did she say.
I remember mom was talking about regret.
Yes! Your mom was wrong!
You can't be like that!
I don't think so.
Even if
my mom really denied her whole life,
I will deny that!
It's fine.
Because we are not mom.
Because we have seen it with our own eyes.
We've seen mom's figure
who discarded everything.
There should be nothing wrong with
the life of someone as kind as her.
You kid talking like you know everything.
You also have been talking in a way
as you know it all.
You don't know how much hope
she found in her children after that.
You are not qualified to talk about her.
Dad.
Mr. Mudo.
Even if at a final moment like now,
I guess you don't have any apologies
for my mom, right?
I will never forgive you.
It can't be a piece of the atonement for your sin.
The day you can be released
from ditching mom will never come!
I came here specially...
It's unsightly, old man.
Bleh!
So it's all cleaned up?
You being you,
everything was witnessed
by you from not far, right?
Well.
Uesugi, thank you.
From the death of mom,
to fill that loneliness,
I was trying to impersonate my mom.
Before I can notice,
the line between mom and me
has become ambiguous.
I didn't have confidence
even in my own dream.
I
don't have to forget about mom!
It's you who taught me about this.
Ugh!
Thank you!
The sky is so dark before I know it.
It's already winter now.
What's the matter suddenly?
It's creepy.
All is blamed on me, sorry.
Anyway,
Thanks to you that I became confident.
I am not mom.
It's because of you that I could
realize such a simple thing.
Although the ideal teacher image of mine
is still like mom...
What?
Well...
In a word,
Uesugi...
You are also ideal for me.
I just wanted you to hear that.
Then,
time for the announcement of the best stall!
(Announcement of the Best Stall)
Best Stall Result
(Class 1 Grade 3)
Class 3 - Group 1
Yay! We did it!
Eh?
Where are the Nakano sisters?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Itsuki, how's it going?
Did you tell Futarou about that?
Yes.
And I also thanked him for dad's affair.
Thank you all again.
It's fine. Never mind.
It was also a problem for our family.
B...But...
Thank...
Thank you!
I could only feel discomfort from that.
What? Girls...
Ah, Miku even disguised like me.
Never mind.
Besides, I'm not satisfied with
such a slipshod disguise.
I see in her there's a mysterious pride
exclusive to her sprouting.
The usual people
will make a mistake just by that.
The face is still the same
even if the contents are different.
We will always be a quintuplet.
Hey!
There's still time
before the appointment with Futarou.
Let's change the mood.
Ah...
How long do you want to sit still here?
How about getting some food at the stalls?
Stalls? Right.
I didn't eat anything.
And there's some stalls I haven't visited.
After that, I...
Still have someone to meet.
I see.
I just saw them if you mean the sisters.
The five are all gathered
as Ichika was also here.
Eh, Maeda?
You figured out Ichika properly in a second.
W...Well.
It maybe weird,
I always could
somehow distinguish Ichika and her only.
Of course Uesugi,
you can figure them out, right?
Huh?
Since you bring that up,
I can't say I'm confident.
I was much more confused than now at first.
To make matters worse,
I'm not good at remembering people's faces.
In addition,
they took full advantage of it.
How many times have I been deceived?
Those who are troublesome until the end.
So bold of you to say that.
I got really curious suddenly.
Since who of the five girls
did you start to be able to distinguish them?
Well, let's go to the stalls.
Wait.
What's up for now?
Hey, Takeda, what does it mean?
You should ask Uesugi about what it means.
It was nothing.
Aren't you too aloof, Uesugi?
Secrets are not allowable between us!
Annoying! That's a secret! Secret!
You like one?
One of the quintuplets.
It is the role of a student to study.
I have grown up believing
that everything else is unnecessary.
But,
there's no need to discard anything else.
Be it study and friendship,
work, entertainment and love,
they were always doing their best.
They taught me that,
filling with the entrenched idea about that.
It's just that I've been keeping them waiting
before I finally realized that not long ago.
If it's the precious me,
I'd still be alone at this moment.
Uesugi...
Well! Let's go to the stalls!
Although I have no money.
Why are you going to the stalls without money?
The resting place really helps!
Yes!
I've decided.
To enjoy this festival until the end.
It's almost the time.
Uesugi,
after everything is over today,
we will be in each room
harboring the though of our own
and waiting for you.
You can head for
only one classroom.
We know that this idea
will confuse you on the contrary.
But this is our resolution.
Please.
Please understand it.
Until now,
School Festival of Asahi Senior School,
closing party,
and all schedules are over.
Uesugi.
You rock, Futarou!
Ah!
It's over.
So at that time...
You have already decided.
This is just the beginning, Uesugi.
Here it is.
Hi.
Huh?
I've been waiting for you.
Eh?
Uesugi, why are you here?
I came to see you.
Yotsuba.
You are joking, right?
Y...You must be joking!
That's impossible!
You're right.
I wonder why it turned out to be like this.
Speaking of that, I'm the one
who've been waiting for long.
Why weren't you here?
Because...
I wasn't expecting your arrival
in any possible way.
I specially bought
the fresh-made fried chicken.
That is...
Didn't you give me the tickets?
Here,
enjoy yourself.
Have you been waiting all the time?
Yes.
I decided to eat with you here.
So...
After getting to know this result,
I'd like to ask.
You...
Sorry!
Ouch!
Eh?
Uesugi?
Hey, Uesugi.
I plucked up my courage and came here.
I didn't expect to be answered instantly.
Well, I got your feeling to me.
I'm so honored, but...
Huh?
There should be someone better for you!
It's a waste to settle by me.
What's going on?
Well, instead of me, the others are...
The others?
I'm asking you right now.
Tell me your feelings.
Hey, you!
She fled.
Uesugi.
Oh!
Itsuki!
Where is she?
I saw Yotsuba running that way.
There's only one destination
you should head for.
Extra consideration could only hurt her.
That's right.
Excuse me.
Yotsuba...
You always said that.
Again and again.
It even got annoying.
Let's make it a school camping trip
with no regrets.
Let's make it a school excursion
Let's make it a school festival
that will not leave any regrets.
I won't give up!
W...Wait!
Sorry, Uesugi.
I can't be the special one.
A girl like me...
Nino.
Where are you?
Ah!
It hurts.
Oops!
Sorry!
No, I didn't pay attention either.
Sorry.
Ah, it's already this late.
Anyway,
let's take the bus home.
Ah.
Huh?
I've spent all my money
on the amulet I bought at the daytime.
Are you a fool?
I've told you I only have...
200 Yen.
I can't lend it to you.
I knew.
Take care.
Huh?
Oops, it's gone.
My family is poor.
I always donated just 5 yen.
Petty, isn't it?
Futarou, don't you feel sad with your money gone?
What do you mean?
It's the same with my family.
For the whole family,
my mom has worked all by herself.
So...
Sometimes I wonder...
Without me...
If mom can be more relieved.
You...
So,
I will study hard,
become super smart,
get into a company that pays well
and make it easier for my mom!
At that time, I'm sure
I'll make my existence meaningful.
Amazing!
You talk like an adult.
- Eh?
- That's right!
If I study hard,
become smart,
and be able to make money too.
I might be able to let my sister live
without any inconvenience.
Maybe I can become someone necessary!
Let's try together!
I, for my mom,
you, for your sister.
Let's study with all our strength!
Yea.
Well,
100 yen each for you and me,
let's pray to the god for that!
Yotsuba...
Eh!
That ribbon suits you very much.
Thank you.
Then you won't take me wrong with the others.
Well, I can't promise that.
Huh?
What you are wearing
is not that big a difference.
Not only this!
I will study harder than others.
I'm the top 1 in last test.
I won, right?
I'm no longer
in the same position with the others.
I'm not exactly the same!
Mom!
Look, look!
Eh, they're very cute.
Like what Yotsuba is doing, I put these on.
Yotsuba,
your hard working is wonderful
and is nothing wrong.
Even if not the best,
each of you is special.
As your parent, I hope
you can all be together.
No matter what happens.
It's not the most important
where you are.
It's important
that all of you five stay together.
She didn't get well at all.
Excuse me.
It's the first time
we speak like this.
I will take the responsibility
and take care of you.
Mom...
We've become junior school students.
But,
it's impossible for all of us to be together.
We
can't stay together anymore.
Dad, look!
In the last exam,
I was the best among the five of us!
Well done.
The track-and-field sports club invited me,
but I refused.
But it can't be helped
as I have to focus on study.
Keep that spirit and move on.
Hum, he's so cold.
If it were mom, I would be praised much more.
I would be praised, right...
Futarou must be studying for now.
Yotsuba, don't you need them anymore?
Yes, because they will
interfere with my study.
So, can I borrow them?
Good, I'm progressing steadily.
I will work harder from now on!
Yotsuba!
I got this score in the history exam!
(Nakano Miku 42 points)
All thanks to the games you lent to me.
R...Really?
That's great...
I have to try harder!
Study hard,
become super smart,
get into a company that pays well...
What am I studying for?
You don't need to be special.
It's important
that all of you five stay together.
Why is it important that we stay together?
I can't understand.
Everyone from track-and-field sports club of
Black Rose Girls High School.
Congratulations on your admission to
the inter-high school competition.
Mom, look.
I'm praised by everyone!
(Congratulations to basketball club
on advancing to the national tournament)
I am reckoned as necessary by many people!
Not any one else of my sisters,
It's me!
You have been practicing all the time recently.
Are you okay? Is it okay with your study?
If you like,
I can teach you.
I am different with you all now!
Don't stay with me.
I'm the best of our sisters.
I'm special!
You failed the second makeup exam.
Nakano Yotsuba,
you have to repeat the year.
That's a joke, right?
No, it's true.
But
I have won so many prizes
in club activities.
At the basketball club, I have just...
They're irrelevant.
You should have been warned repeatedly.
But you didn't stop joining in multiple clubs.
Pack your luggage.
(Principal's Office)
Eh?
Transferring?
It's a coeducational school
where my acquaintance works as a director.
From the end of summer vacation,
you will start to study there.
Only me?
Eh?
I should be special...
I was trying so desperately
to make my existence meaningful.
Why am I alone?
If I'm alone,
what should I do?
What should I do to be special?
I don't know where should I head for.
Wait.
Ah!
If Yotsuba transfers,
we will go with her.
What are you saying?
You should have passed the exam.
Yes, we passed.
Thanks to "cheating".
I...Is that true?
We too.
Girls...
Why?
Why do you do that for me?
Yotsuba,
although I don't know
what you are thinking.
Leaving by your own
is something I absolutely hate!
We will always stay together
wherever we go.
That is what mom has taught us.
Yotsuba...
Everything can be divided into
five equal parts by all of us.
Even difficulties
can be overcome by we five.
Now I understand
what my mom's words mean.
Stop thinking about who's the best.
I'll live on for everyone.
Eh?
100 points?
W...Wait!
Because of all my sisters,
I can be who I am currently.
Both that memory and this feeling,
I'll just erase them.
Ouch!
Ah!
Are you okay?
Your sisters are all so nice,
so amazing,
and girls I like so much.
I'm proud of being your tutor.
But... If there weren't you,
I would have stumbled already.
Why did you say so?
I am so infirm a person.
I will continue to stumble
for many times in the future.
It's a selfish wish of me who is so wack.
At such moments, Yotsuba,
I would be happy if you are by my side.
I would be relieved.
You are my support.
I also want to become your support.
So, it's fine if you dislike it.
Please tell me your feeling.
I...
Uesugi.
Say it
and put an end to all these.
I hate Uesugi.
Hate... Hate... Hate...
I like you!
I...
can't...
tell lies to you.
I have been in love with you.
But...
Sorry.
Ah!
There's still something I have to do.
(Math) (Nakano Ichika)
Eh? You are not dating?
Actually...
I see.
You are not dating.
If so,
Futarou still
doesn't belong to anyone.
Hey, cheer up!
Didn't Yotsuba say she likes you?
Then it's a mutual love.
You may be disliked if you worry too much.
Right.
Thank you.
Ichika.
Even if someday he chose you,
I would be willing to congratulate you.
I came to understand
what Nino said before.
You should have known
that I have been in love with Fu.
You must have known that
and waited for yesterday, right?
I don't want and need your concern anymore.
But I am concerned.
Nino, you are an important family for me!
If so,
it's done for you and me.
If you two keep that way,
the relationship of sisters
will be cut off.
Yotsuba.
Your body will get cold
if you stay here.
Miku.
I am Yotsuba.
What?
I was thinking.
As he didn't choose me,
I could just dress like Yotsuba
and date Futarou. That's my plan.
How about it?
I don't think it'll work.
Moralistically.
C...Cold...
Let's change the place.
It's the first time
that only two of us come to the karaoke.
Yotsuba.
What?
I was just joking.
Dressing up like Yotsuba
is a joke.
Although I can imitate Yotsuba,
I can't become you.
This juice
is too sweet for me.
Miku...
But I'm mad at you.
If it's me,
I won't do anything
that will confuse Futarou.
You are hesitating about the answer, right?
I thought your favorable feeling
towards Futarou
should not be a little.
I'm not hesitating.
My feelings have never changed
since before.
I have been thinking about Uesugi.
If that's the case,
there should be less reasons
for you to hesitate.
Are you still minding
what happened in the previous school?
Don't mind us.
It's fine to date him.
Ah...
You thought I'd say something like that?
I knew I should...
However,
what is regrettable is regrettable.
Whatever,
I couldn't help but feel intense inside.
That's my true feelings.
If...
Yotsuba also thinks so,
I hope you can also take
the feelings of us.
Nino's feelings.
I didn't manage to understand it.
It's natural that she got mad.
Nino said so.
Because of love,
we are not enemies or companions.
I see.
If you can think that way,
then please forgive our last resistance.
Absolutely,
we can never give you any supportive nudge.
It's rare chance. So let's sing!
Right! Listen to me.
I will sing better than you, Miku!
Could ask nothing better.
Wow, look!
It's such a nice day!
(Karaoke Samurai)
I didn't expected to keep singing
all over the night.
Hey, Miku.
I...
want to meet everyone!
Yotsuba got one thing wrong.
I purposely didn't tell her that.
That time,
she made the choice to come to this school,
so we could meet Futarou.
At least
I don't find it's unfortunate.
Because we could meet Futarou.
I...
Let's go, Yotsuba.
Although
I couldn't become Yotsuba,
Yotsuba can't become me either.
Finally,
the more I think this way,
the fonder I've become of myself.
Itsuki.
Can I have a word with you?
What's the matter?
Well. I have something to talk to you.
It might not be appropriate to talk here.
So, come here.
Well... What do you want to say?
S...Sorry.
It hurts... Well, don't mind.
I can always feel it.
This pent-up feeling in my chest.
Is it empty here?
The one who disturbed
the harmony of we quintuplets.
Yotsuba, is you.
Sorry to be selfish.
I didn't think about
your feelings yesterday, Nino.
I imposed too much on you.
But
I still have the same thought.
I hope...
I'm shocked.
You are still saying such naive words.
I won't admit it...
Eh?!
Was it just a mouse?
There are mice here.
That's was close.
Kinda impossible to open the door, right?
Please don't get too close to me.
In such a place,
I don't want to be seen
by Yotsuba and the others.
The lunch break is almost over.
Let's go back.
Wait!
What!
I came to tell you with my own resolution.
I hope
you can admit my relationship with Uesugi.
- I said that is...
- But!
It doesn't have to be now!
Months later...
Years later...
I don't know how much time it will cost,
but I know how much
I am in love with Uesugi.
The strength of this feeling!
I want to show it to you!
I will never lose!
That's right.
No matter how you apologize
or persuade now,
I can't accept it.
After understanding that,
you're going on the thorny path.
Just as I like Uesugi,
I also like all my sisters.
Come on, you stupid.
But that's as expected of Yotsuba.
You're now finally unleashed from the shackles
of the quintuplets and rush forward.
I don't like to see your back,
but I'm jealous.
Maybe you are still taking me
as an opponent to compete.
Of course.
We have been growing up
while being aware of each other.
Sometimes we are companions.
Sometimes we are enemies.
That is...
We are
rivals!
The game is not over here!
I'll keep observing you two
from a little behind.
If even the slightest gap is shown,
I will take him away!
Uh-huh!
It's time for us to end this talk.
Come out, you two mice!
Have you found out...
Well, well...
Uesugi!
Itsuka!
Were you two listening all the time?
Sorry.
You heard it, right, Fu?
In that case,
never let you guard down.
Well, I will bear it in mind deeply.
Seems you also have captured
the most difficult heart of our sisters.
But,
I can finally say it.
You
are not alone.
Uesugi,
Congratulations.
I sincerely appreciate it
that you invited me out.
Sorry to ask you out during the holiday.
N...No. Not at all.
I am happy.
Really?
After all,
we couldn't be alone at school.
Exactly.
We don't know
if someone is listening somewhere.
Ouch!
Emergency stop for falling objects check.
- Sorry for the inconvenience.
- Aren't we supposed to be in the opposite positions?
- Please wait a moment for the security confirmation.
- Right...
Well, order whatever you like!
It's on me!
Wow! Delicious!
That's great.
It's really irritating.
Why is the destination of their date
a family restaurant?
I think it's fresh and good.
Can I use this?
He's using a coupon.
Can't he?
It's no good to use a coupon during a date.
It's a way of trying for Futarou.
(Vegetable Festival)
You accepted the offer of the athletic college, right?
(The Sound of Far Mountains)
Yes!
So... is it your dream?
Do you want to become an athlete?
No.
I've forgotten my dream as a child.
But after all,
I think it will be suitable for me
to be helpful and supportive for others.
I only started to think like that after giving up.
But now I have realized
that I can be proud of that too.
I see.
That's what you would do.
I started to think like this
when you said so.
Is it so?
Yes!
So, if I can enroll into college,
I want to find a job
that I can support others by study.
Oh, Yeah.
(Keep Quiet in Library) (Psychology)
I'm getting impatient.
Hold down, hold down.
I'm sorry.
It's so boring in library.
No!
If it's with you,
everything is so fun.
Then,
can you go to the last place with me?
Yes!
Yotsuba,
it seems you're fine
without a push on your back.
Here is...
It's so nostalgic.
You
liked this swing, right?
Am I not supposed to be taken to somewhere
you have strong feelings about today?
Yes.
The family restaurant my family usually visits.
The library I usually study at.
Since the day I came here with you,
this place has become one of them.
Is it okay?
To be honest, I'm still hesitating.
Is it OK that
I put all my sisters aside,
be so happy by myself?
Is this a right choice?
You can jump so far here, right?
Show me again!
Okay!
It's a piece of cake.
Now!
How about it?
Yotsuba.
If I can jump over there,
can I ask you something?
Well...
I'm coming.
No, don't push yourself too hard!
Behold.
Further...
I should be able to go further!
Oops!
Died?
Yotsuba.
Such an inexperienced person
who can't handle a date...
But
I will devote myself to become a man
standing next to you.
No matter the right path
or the wrong path,
let's go ahead together.
So,
if you like
come with me.
I...
I love you.
Will you marry me?
Eh?
I am so shocked!
I... Certainly...
You've skipped so many steps!
T...That's right.
It's too fast.
Proposing before the dating
could only scare off the girl!
I mean if that girl is not me.
Sorry.
Please let me do it again.
Yotsuba?
I remembered my dream
as a child.
It's something everyone longs for.
An ordinary dream.
To be a bride.
Uesugi,
promise me.
Someday,
please realize my dream.
A...Actually, to you all...
To you all,
I have to say something.
About the college I'm going to enter,
though I kept silent about it,
it's in Tokyo!
Eh? We have known that.
Huh?
We didn't ask about it intentionally.
But we guess you would do so.
That's right.
We don't mind it at all.
Ah, really...
Try your best at the exam.
We can go to see you any time.
Thank you.
I'm glad to meet you.
See you.
See you tomorrow.
Just like our expectation.
He seems to be unusually lonely.
But
maybe also a little happy.
Being able to see
such a face of Uesugi,
it's so lucky.
Idiot!
Didn't we decided not to cry?
That's all because of Nino!
(Technical School of Cook)
Let us enjoy cooking
delicious food
Culinary Arts
College
Basics of Cooking
& Confectionary
(Basic of Cooking & Confectionery)
Dreams or goals...
I wonder if I can be like you too.
You can do it for sure, Nino.
You are one of us.
Just a little more,
I'll stick with you.
I see. Thank you.
(January)
Long time no see.
(Qualification Notice
Candidate Name Nakano Nino)
(Congratulations for Qualification
of Technical School)
(February)
Nakano!
It's your turn!
I'm coming.
(List of Passers for the Entrance Exam
of the Education University)
List of successful applicants for the Entrance Exam
Mom!
I,
made it!
Hey, Yotsuba.
You need to live alone
if you enter the college.
Are you really fine with it?
Ichika, you are worried all the time.
I don't worry being away.
Because,
we all...
Are you being nervous? That's not like you.
Maybe.
But, I am not alone.
For sure...
So do they.
(Nakano)
(Five Years Later)
5 years later
Ichika will come soon.
Well,
let's also get ready.
It's a long-awaited gathering.
(Groom Uesugi Futarou
Bride Nakano Yotsuba)
Wedding invitation
It would be a rather small one,
Bride Groom: Uesugi Futarou
Bride: Nakano Yotsuba
This country has not changed a bit.
I'm back, Japan!
Didn't you just go on a trip?
Itsuki!
Thank you for being here for me.
You are famous now.
Keep a low profile. Keep a low profile.
Welcome.
Oh.
It's you.
Ichika, long time no see.
I'm glad you both look fine.
Your cafe also seems very popular.
As expected of Americanization,
you got good at jokes.
How about it
when you were in America actually?
I'm still worried about my Intoneshon.
Ichika.
It's intonation.
You are so strict.
I'm now a teacher.
Do you want to eat?
It's ready now.
Yay!
Humph, I wonder if it's palatable
for someone who went to
such a pretentious cafe.
Eh?
Did I tell you I went there?
Nino has been keeping her eyes
on your Instagram, Ichika.
Miku, don't say it!
Really?
As a token of thanks,
I will share your store on my Instagram.
Wait.
Attracted by your popularity,
there will definitely be more customers.
Though I'm happy,
please refrain it for now.
There are more and more
regulate customers recently.
Also as dad provided
such a well-equipped place,
I want to give it
a little more try by ourselves.
What?
I'm proud of you, my sister!
I won't be embarrassed
to mention you on any occasion.
When you run out of popularity,
we can offer you a job.
You are not adorable at all.
She's cute in her own way.
Huh?
Girls, the leading role of today comes.
Thank you for gathering!
Why are you so sweaty?
I couldn't stay still somehow.
I rode a bike here from home.
Rode a bike?
Eh?
What are you doing right
before such an important ceremony?
But I suppose
Uesugi is coming by metro, right?
Yes. Futarou came back yesterday.
So he's still sleeping...
Eh? What?
Finally you have to admit it
that you're living together.
Humph, that's why you
started to call secretly from the morning.
Ah!
My make-up artist might come to help.
Are we really going to do that?
What are you scared of?
You were excited about it, weren't you?
Right.
We have to confirm that with Uesugi.
Ichika.
I've been wearing it.
These are our presents for your marriage.
Mom's keepsake earrings.
Yotsuba, you are prepared, right?
Yes, please.
Let's get start, girls.
Here we go!
Yotsuba, congratulations on your marriage.
It hurts!
Groom.
Here comes a family of the bride.
Great.
I wondered if you would come.
Why didn't you show up
during the ceremony?
Sorry.
Come or not,
I was considering until just before.
D...Dad!
There's no reason for you to call me dad.
Thank you sincerely for your coming.
I'm sorry I was so rude
when I was younger...
Uesugi.
Let me ask directly.
Yes.
Is Yotsuba happy from heart?
Me too.
Let's have some wine.
Eh?
Ah. Okay. I'll open it for you.
Well.
Futarou's waiting room is...
My mom died
more than 10 years ago.
The accident happened
right after the opening of her own restaurant,
which was my mother's dream.
Only a large amount of debt borrowed
for opening funds was left in my home.
My dad lent that vacant store to Nino and Miku.
One reason is to help them,
and maybe the other
is to entrust them with mom's dream.
Love a woman with the whole life.
I want to become such a man.
Just like my two dads.
Stop it.
Sorry.
I'm not use to it.
Something as being called dad.
Groom.
The bride wants to see you.
Please come with me.
Well...
Go ahead.
Maruo.
We are also elders now.
We can only drink some wine
for congratulations?
Yes...
That's why I'm drinking.
Do you think it will go well for them?
Such a thing
is not something can be decided as a parent.
But,
I'm sure it won't be that straightforward.
Anyhow, his opponents
are my daughters.
Futarou, it's the last quintuplets game.
If there's love,
you can distinguish us.
Dear guests, excuse me for interrupting you
when you are so busy.
Thank you for coming to
our wedding reception today.
Quintuplets game...
Are you idiots!?
The other four except Yotsuba!
Don't wear a wedding dress for fun!
Do you know what you are doing?
It's really a little difficult.
I came up with it.
And it's not for fun.
Eh?
Because we are relatives of the bride.
Kidding.
I am the bride myself.
No, I am.
It's me the bride!
Futarou, you should know.
Come on, you fool.
Just when I think
that you've become sensible adults,
I feel relieved
that you have never changed.
Don't take me for a fool.
It's you.
Thanks again to my families.
Thanks to
my dad, mom,
and my sisters, I can be who I am now.
I'm glad that
you can be my dad.
You are Ichika.
The first daughter Ichika,
is an older sister who brings together
a bunch of girls with different personalities.
As you all know, she's a very popular actress
and an existence I've been looking up to.
What?
I'm so surprised.
I missed it.
I was bothered by you so much.
Isn't the whole world calling you as cool beauty?
You can't deceive me.
Sluttish! Crass! Idle your time away!
Lazy!
You don't need to say that much...
Even though...
The figure trying to be strong
looked dazzling to me.
You're the great eldest daughter.
The next is you.
Nino.
The second daughter Nino,
is a little irritable.
But she's strong and strict.
She's a elder sister who can always
push our back forward.
She's got outstanding girl power,
that I also have to emulate.
Yes, correct.
Yea, yea. Good for you.
Why at such a time...
You could have just pointed out Yotsuba...
Your toughness
comes from the fact that
you're quite fragile more than others.
As well as your strictness.
I wonder if it's because
you have that much love.
At that time,
I wasn't able to find out the answer.
Sorry.
It's fine.
I don't regret.
Really?
You are Miku.
Yes.
The third daughter Miku
doesn't feel like an elder sister unexpectedly.
She may be more likely as a close friend
who has been in the same position.
So, of course,
I respect Miku who has realized
her own dream.
I'm sometimes anxious.
Can I do it well?
Needless to answer.
You've always been struggling with
yourself like that.
Such victory of your inner battle
is no doubt credited to yourself.
Believe in yourself.
You have always been capable since before.
I expected you to say that.
Thank you, Futarou.
Then only you left, Itsuki.
Eh?
I am Yotsuba...
I'm kidding.
Ta-dah! I'm Itsuki.
How about it? I've been better at it, right?
Itsuki is my only younger sister
who is so cute.
Actually she has been
much better than me all the time.
When I am confused about what to do,
it's also Itsuki who pushed my back forward.
This is...
I can't barely hold it.
At such a moment, I must tell you.
After meeting you!
My life started to go crazy!
Source of evil! Curry-eating glutton girl!
It's the same with me!
Before I met you,
I couldn't imagine a person
with no delicacy like you!
Big-headed! Natural kiss demon!
I really can't get along with you
for my whole life!
Itsuki returned to the former tone she talked.
It can't be helped.
The opponent is Futarou.
I've been striving to live in my own way.
And you are
Yotsuba.
Yes. That's correct.
Without my sisters,
my life will be completely different.
As one of the quintuplets,
sometimes I felt beholden.
But I also remember the fun
I share with my sisters
that is hundreds of times
more than the burden.
I've been staying with you for so long,
I can remember even if I don't like it.
Although I was your tutor,
it's you who have taught me a lot.
Being able to meet you quintuplets,
is one of the few things I'm proud of.
I feel it so happy being able
to be one of the quintuplets
and grow up with you girls.
We are a little different
from the other families.
It may be strange from others' perspective.
I love such a family so much!
Five years...
I guess for now everything
could settle down.
My tension finally went away
and feel exhausted all of a sudden.
It turns out you also felt nervous.
Although not as much as you, Futarou.
Your hands were shaking
during the kiss of oath.
It can't be helped!
Everyone was watching.
With you...
It reminded me of
what happened 5 years ago...
After all, that is...
Bride.
You lost something in the waiting room.
Oh, thank you!
Sorry.
I don't need it anymore.
Please discard it for me.
Huh?
Okay.
Is it okay?
Isn't it your trademark?
It's fine.
Each of you is special.
No matter how exactly we look...
There's always someone
who can figure me out.
What are you doing?
Well done.
It's a good ceremony.
You ask what are we doing?
There's only one thing to do
after the ceremony.
The honeymoon!
Huh? Wait...
Do you all want to go with us?
(Egypt Guidebook)
Of course.
We are undecided about the destination.
You really have a strong personality.
It's much happier with all together.
Right?
Yes, yes!
If so, point out where you want to go.
As Yotsuba said so...
I feel like we disputed about
the same thing before.
Oh, in high school!
Let's get started.
Here we go!
Uesugi, get up.
Good morning.
Looking at Futarou,
I also want to have a sleep.
You could catch a cold.
Don't sleep here and get up quickly.
How about the wedding?
What?
That's so hasty.
Stop being half asleep,
and decide quickly.
Eh?
Decide what?
The graduation trip.
Isn't it you who proposed it, Futarou?
I...Is that so...
An...Anyway, let us five point
where we want to go.
How about me?
We all know what's gonna happen though.
I wonder if I should quit...
So let's start with"here we go".
Hey!
Here we go!
I want to see Sakamoto Ryoma.
Isn't it the same spot with the excursion?
Let's go to Okinawa.
There are a lot of delicious food in Hokkaido.
There are lots of wonderful destinations.
Girls, let's decide it by rock-paper-scissors!
That's right...
I think it's the same with that time.
Oops...
Completely different.
How about Futarou?
The quintuplets are so annoying.
“Ari
ga
tou”
no
ha
na
saku
tabi
Every time a "Thank You" blooms
“Ari
ga
tou”
no
ha
na
saku
rii~
tabi
This story shines.
Mune
ni
daite
aru
ite
yukou
Subarashii~
too
Let's Keep it in our hearts and move forward.
Mune
ni
daite
yukou
Today is wonderful, it is beautiful
Subarashii~
The days that we spent together
Like they were a routine
When we laugh, cry and joke,
They are like an album
And the important things get bigger every time we open it up
shii~
I can still remember,
How I felt.
It is nostalgic
La~ la~ la~ la~
se
ru
La~
la~
“Ari
ga
tou”
The "Thank You"s are overflowing
“Ari
ga
tou”
afu
Kimi
yoka
tta~
te
I'm glad you are here.
ku
Kimi
kasa
wa,
mirai
ga~
yoka
I can feel something warm in my heart. That signal,
kasa
sain
ne~
mirai
marks the beginning of the future.
Ha
ji
ma
ru
“Ari
ga
tou”
tabi
Every time a "Thank You" blooms, our story shines
ku
sutoo
rii~
sain
“Ari
ga
tou”
tabi
You can continue to
sutoo
ra
shii~
Today is wonderful, it is beautiful
sometimes,
kke~
When we fight.
An "I'm Sorry"...
I cannot say.
I tried to be stubborn,
but I was weak.
If you notice,
My shape will be restored
The truth is that I am still alone
I feel that you are moving away from me.
chau,
Ni
te
ru
ne~
Although I am happy, I started to cry.
chau,
It is something like the sadness of first love.
tou”
"Thank You" is a promise. Let's make this great love grow
wo
ha
gu
ku
mou~
“A
ri
ga
tou”
Yes, you'll be fine with it, I'm proud of you.
ku
ra
shii~
Today will be beautiful one,
Forever and ever, Forever and ever,
from now on...